<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv date="20250717090907 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403837/20250717.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403837&amp;date=20250717&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403837">
    <display-name lang="US">Disney XD USA - Eastern Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717000000 +0000" stop="20250717003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip wants to make a breakfast that will blow his friends' socks off; Larry saves a baby lizard and swears to protect it from harm.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717003000 +0000" stop="20250717010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater helps Toñita hide a secret from Tere and Tabi; Tater tries to host a sleepover while hiding the cousins.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717010000 +0000" stop="20250717013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff's thirst for life takes her on countless adventures through their city alongside her best friend, Barry.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717013000 +0000" stop="20250717020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff's thirst for life takes her on countless adventures through their city alongside her best friend, Barry.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717020000 +0000" stop="20250717023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace uses Phineas and Ferb's newest invention to gain height she needs for a modeling career; the boys build an aquarium in their backyard.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717023000 +0000" stop="20250717030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb are inspired by Candace's dessert club; Candace and Stacey assume the roles of Sherlock Holmes and Watson to try to bust the boys in London.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717030000 +0000" stop="20250717033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket is caught eating dog food by Gloria and must stop her from revealing his secret shame; Bill installs a parenting device to monitor and discipline Cricket for him.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717033000 +0000" stop="20250717040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill and Cricket follow clues from Cricket's dream to search the woods for the perfect Christmas tree; Tilly catches ennui, so Cricket tries to cheer her up.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717040000 +0000" stop="20250717043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill begrudgingly joins Cricket to cover up a turkey-related crime on Thanksgiving; the Greens get into crazy hijinks in a Smalton antique shop.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717043000 +0000" stop="20250717050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket tries to avoid a fortune teller's ominous prediction that he will get a stinky slap; in an inescapable escape room, Cricket must decide between family and freedom.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717050000 +0000" stop="20250717053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>While Stan, Dipper, Mabel and Soos are falling in a bottomless pit, they tell stories to pass time.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717053000 +0000" stop="20250717060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>When Mabel befriends a cute merman trapped in the deep end of the public pool, she's determined to return him to his family in the ocean, even though that means her whirlwind romance will come to an end; Dipper learns that Wendy is a lifeguard.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717060000 +0000" stop="20250717063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>Luz, Willow and Amity take a stroll down memory lane to reclaim Willow's memories when Amity accidentally destroys them.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717063000 +0000" stop="20250717070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>Luz experiences Grom, Hexside's version of prom; it is not what she expects.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717070000 +0000" stop="20250717073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Larry must confront his jealousy or be consumed by it; to keep a secret, Lullah is forced to help Pliny assist a grub.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717073000 +0000" stop="20250717080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>A spiraling Merian tries to figure out exactly why Francis left her party; the kids vie for a presidential sash.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717080000 +0000" stop="20250717083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill and Nancy prep a special harvest dinner; Cricket and Gramma race Tilly to get a missing ingredient; at the local community center, Tilly wants to win a trophy and begins training with the center's director.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717083000 +0000" stop="20250717090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly tries ventriloquism for the Big Coffee open mic night; the family plays the people-watching game, making up stories about city folk passing by.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717090000 +0000" stop="20250717093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The Greens go on a family visit to the dentist's office, where Cricket is determined to avoid Dr. Enamel and power through his toothache.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717093000 +0000" stop="20250717100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Nancy's trailer is stolen by her old biker gang, the kids resolve to get it back; Cricket house-sits for Remy, but things go awry when the rest of the Greens visit.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717100000 +0000" stop="20250717103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Remy uses Cricket's antics to gain views and likes on a new video-sharing app; Gloria gives Tilly and Cricket a tour of the animation studio where she's interning.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717103000 +0000" stop="20250717110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket tries to prove to Bill he can eat fast food for every meal; Tilly and Cricket debate whether the lives of people in Big City are connected.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717110000 +0000" stop="20250717113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket teaches the local kids a new curse word, threatening to ruin the community center's choir performance; the Greens try new methods to improve sales at their produce stand.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717113000 +0000" stop="20250717120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill chaperones Cricket and Gabriella's first date; a disagreement between Cricket and Tilly turns into reality-TV-like entertainment for Gloria and Gramma.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717120000 +0000" stop="20250717123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When the kids play a role-playing game at Remy's, his rules lead to conflict; when the Greens go out for karaoke, Tilly struggles to decide what genre of music will best express her true self.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717123000 +0000" stop="20250717130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>On New Year's Eve, Cricket insists on helping Gloria complete her resolution of approaching her crush, Kevin; Cricket and Remy challenge Vasquez to a snowball fight; Tilly creates a snowperson.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717130000 +0000" stop="20250717133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Gloria's parents visit, she ropes the Greens into escalating lies about her success; Cricket goes on a quest to find the best pool in Big City.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717133000 +0000" stop="20250717140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Chip Whistler tears down the buildings around the Green's house to build a Wholesome Foods store.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717140000 +0000" stop="20250717143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>At the library, the Greens try to find a book, but a scary librarian threatens them into being quiet; Chip decides if he is really the failure Cricket says he is.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717143000 +0000" stop="20250717150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket struggles to get the best birthday present for his best bud, Remy; due to a close call with a dirt bike, Cricket fearfully decides to live his life in shelter.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717150000 +0000" stop="20250717153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Remy put on a play; Cricket meets his favorite heroes; when Gramma temporarily loses her eyesight, Cricket and Tilly try to help her.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717153000 +0000" stop="20250717160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When the Greens visit BigTech, Tilly discovers a chance to improve her family; Cricket wins tickets to a show and must decide who to bring.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717160000 +0000" stop="20250717163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Cricket's crush returns, Remy takes the opportunity to help Cricket get to know her; the family wants to visit a street fair, but Bill wants to stay home to save money.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717163000 +0000" stop="20250717170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Perry wins a contest and becomes the spokesanimal for Totally Tools.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717170000 +0000" stop="20250717173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb create their own language, Ferb Latin; The boys clone potatoes when all of them go missing in Danville.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717173000 +0000" stop="20250717180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Crikey the Crocodile has gone missing.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717180000 +0000" stop="20250717183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb think up a new game; volleyball with jet-packs.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717183000 +0000" stop="20250717190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb set off to find the legendary sword, Excaliferb in order to defeat an evil sorcerer named Millifishmirtz.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717190000 +0000" stop="20250717193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>The final clash of the All-Star Battle is underway. When the dust settles, Quinn offers her opinions on what makes a true Blader.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717193000 +0000" stop="20250717200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Zed, Addison and the Seabrook crew get to redo their senior year together; Zed creates a new drink called zoda that transforms the entire school into zoda-obsessed zombies.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717200000 +0000" stop="20250717203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Eliza and Bucky compete to see whose vending machine is better; Zed and Addison use their free period to help the stressed-out A-spen learn to let loose.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717203000 +0000" stop="20250717210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>When Willa's favorite boots go missing, she teams up with Lost 'n Found Detective Bree to track them down; Zed and Addison's clones turn on them and try to steal their lives.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717210000 +0000" stop="20250717213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Wynter and A-spen start a band, but they may not reconcile their differing musical visions; Willa and Bucky put Wyatt through an alpha-dog-bootcamp to help him win over Eliza.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717213000 +0000" stop="20250717220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Bucky turns the school into a Bucky-themed dystopia; when Bonzo discovers mysterious blueprints in the diner, he becomes possessed by the desire to build a Spaghetti Waterfall.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717220000 +0000" stop="20250717223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Addison is determined to help Dae, the quirky new witch at school, feel welcome; Zed and little sister Zoey must team up to fight a monster hunter.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717223000 +0000" stop="20250717230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>The stress of directing the school play causes Addison's alien energy to fritz; Wyatt teams up with Eliza to help him keep a secret from the wolf pack.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717230000 +0000" stop="20250717233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Eliza and Wyatt both want to ask the other to the school dance, but mishaps keep getting in their way; feeling pressure to plan her future, Wynter uses VR to find her dream job.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250717233000 +0000" stop="20250718000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ZOMBIES: The Re-Animated Series Shorts</title>
    <desc>Continuing the adventures of fan favorites Zed, Addison and the Seabrook crew.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718000000 +0000" stop="20250718010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">ZOMBI-Thon With Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The Green family from "Big City Greens" reacts to shorts based on the movie "Z-O-M-B-I-E-S.".</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718010000 +0000" stop="20250718013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>A trip to the aquarium! Kiff worries that she's annoying.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718013000 +0000" stop="20250718020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry accompany Trollie on a mission to his magical neighborhood; the Chatterley family heads to Okaywill for new winter coats.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718020000 +0000" stop="20250718023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace tries to find where her brother's wild creations go when they disappear; Chez Platypus becomes the most-trendy restaurant in town.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718023000 +0000" stop="20250718030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb care for an egg they believe belongs to Perry; the boys create their own video game starring themselves.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718030000 +0000" stop="20250718033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>To prove to his parents that he is money-wise, Remy starts his own business; feeling neglected by his family, Bill befriends a murder of crows.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718033000 +0000" stop="20250718040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>A nature documentary portrays Big City as a wild ecosystem; avid collector Remy struggles to cope after Cricket finds the rarest of all trading cards.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718040000 +0000" stop="20250718043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill just wants Tilly to come down from a tree; when Remy tells Vasquez that he no longer needs his protection, Vasquez speaks with a therapist.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718043000 +0000" stop="20250718050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly goes down an internet rabbit hole to figure out what happened to her favorite ice cream treat; Cricket tries to teach Gregly how to make friends.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718050000 +0000" stop="20250718053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Mabel and Dipper stumble upon a hidden room inside the Mystery Shack.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718053000 +0000" stop="20250718060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>When Mabel discovers that her favorite boy band is actually a bunch of imprisoned clones, she sets them free, only to decide on keeping them for herself; Dipper is convinced that Robbie plans to brainwash Wendy with a secret message.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718060000 +0000" stop="20250718063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>It's Grudgby season at Hexside and Boshca is being extra mean towards Willow and her friends; Willow must take on Boscha at Grudgby, to protect her friends and stop them from being used for target practise.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718063000 +0000" stop="20250718070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>On a school field trip to the mysterious Emperor's Castle, Luz puts herself in danger.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718070000 +0000" stop="20250718073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Merian tries to save Dr. Lullah's fish counter from a life of busy work; the kids put on a play to warn mutants about a disaster.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718073000 +0000" stop="20250718080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Kids face fears to retrieve lost ball as Lullah tricks them into devious game.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718080000 +0000" stop="20250718083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>At the Valentine's Dance, Cricket develops an unwanted crush on Gabriella; Cricket joins forces with Officer Keys to hunt down a neighborhood litterbug.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718083000 +0000" stop="20250718090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma spurns Tilly at the city park, so Tilly tries making her jealous; Gramma makes special biscuits for the kids when they're hurt, but won't make more when they're better.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250718090000 +0000" stop="20250719000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket stages a crisis by letting skunks into the cafe, but it gets out of control; Nancy accidentally destroys Saxon, but Tilly mistakenly directs her wrath at Gramma.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-18</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
