<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv date="20250707090937 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403837/20250707.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403837&amp;date=20250707&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403837">
    <display-name lang="US">Disney XD USA - Eastern Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707000000 +0000" stop="20250707003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace puts Mom in a Candace costume in hopes that she'll finally see the boys' invention; Stacy takes on an agent role with OWCA to rescue Perry from some evil scientists.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707003000 +0000" stop="20250707010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Doof becomes a mothman; the boys make a movie set.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707010000 +0000" stop="20250707013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Meap enlists Candace and the kids to help bust his nemesis, Mitch, before he can steal a long-lost treasure hidden somewhere on Earth.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707013000 +0000" stop="20250707020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>A digital phantom of his younger self haunts Zedy; Addison must find a way to silence her inner critic before she gives up on art altogether.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707020000 +0000" stop="20250707023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Zed and his friends find a mini fridge, but it is too mini for them to share; Bree wants to get into the Cheer Hall(way) of Fame, but a negative comment destroys her confidence.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707023000 +0000" stop="20250707030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Eliza and Wyatt both want to ask the other to the school dance, but mishaps keep getting in their way; feeling pressure to plan her future, Wynter uses VR to find her dream job.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707030000 +0000" stop="20250707033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>After being mocked for his handshake, Cricket trains for a Western-style handshake duel; Gloria combines her work life and social life by hiring her friends as employees.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707033000 +0000" stop="20250707040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma butts heads with Nick when he crashes her special family hockey outing; Chip Whistler recounts what happened to him since "Chipocalypse Now.".</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707040000 +0000" stop="20250707043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Kids face fears to retrieve lost ball as Lullah tricks them into devious game.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707043000 +0000" stop="20250707050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>LEAPIN LEGS! Merian is sent to a special place to learn how to relax. NICE TO PEAT YOU! Pliny dislodges a naturalist from a bog and joins him on a journey of discovery.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707050000 +0000" stop="20250707053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>The kids get sucked into a white-hot, Mutant soap opera; Sara attempts to nail the perfect hairstyle so she can be the star of Francis' painting.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707053000 +0000" stop="20250707063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip becomes a spy to prove he's not a nincompoop; after a close call, daredevil Larry embraces a life of extreme caution.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707063000 +0000" stop="20250707080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater's pride in her artwork is deflated by criticism; Tater tries to track down the town's missing dogs.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707080000 +0000" stop="20250707083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Nancy's trailer is stolen by her old biker gang, the kids resolve to get it back; Cricket house-sits for Remy, but things go awry when the rest of the Greens visit.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707083000 +0000" stop="20250707090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>At the Valentine's Dance, Cricket develops an unwanted crush on Gabriella; Cricket joins forces with Officer Keys to hunt down a neighborhood litterbug.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707090000 +0000" stop="20250707093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma spurns Tilly at the city park, so Tilly tries making her jealous; Gramma makes special biscuits for the kids when they're hurt, but won't make more when they're better.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707093000 +0000" stop="20250707100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket stages a crisis by letting skunks into the cafe, but it gets out of control; Nancy accidentally destroys Saxon, but Tilly mistakenly directs her wrath at Gramma.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707100000 +0000" stop="20250707103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>To impress his new neighbors, Cricket attempts to launch a chicken into space; the Greens are excited to continue their traditional monthly steak dinner, but Cricket accidentally loses the steaks on the subway.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707103000 +0000" stop="20250707110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket must wrestle a wild animal in order to prove himself worthy of the family name; when Cricket persuades Bill to convert his pickup into a french fry food truck, he discovers a mysterious blue potato that Gramma says is cursed with bad luck.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707110000 +0000" stop="20250707113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When the Greens visit an indoor pool, Cricket is challenged to jump off the high dive; Tilly claims that the family's goat has the spirit of a dog and enters it in a dog show.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707113000 +0000" stop="20250707120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Gramma crashes into a parked police car, she loses her driver's license and her confidence; Cricket Green hates bears.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707120000 +0000" stop="20250707123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill takes the family on a road trip to the country, only to wind up trapped in a traffic jam; when Tilly finds a bird's nest, she cares for the eggs hoping the chicks will think she's their mother, but the birds imprint on Cricket instead.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707123000 +0000" stop="20250707130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill takes Gramma to a doctor's checkup and leaves Tilly in charge of Cricket; Cricket learns that Bill never realized his childhood dream of becoming a gymnast.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707130000 +0000" stop="20250707133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket Green and his family move from the country to Big City to live with Gramma; when Cricket and Bill accidentally disturb a nest of raccoons in the garage, they invade the house.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707133000 +0000" stop="20250707140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill promises his family a trip to the mall food court; when he reveals it was just a trick to get them to a family portrait studio, Cricket and Gramma try to escape; Remy is caught skipping his violin lessons to hang out with Cricket.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707140000 +0000" stop="20250707143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>While dining at a seafood restaurant, Bill feels he must prove to the waiter that he is a Big City local, and Cricket and Tilly try to rescue a live octopus; when Cricket loses all of his critterballs over the fence, Gloria refuses to return them.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707143000 +0000" stop="20250707150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket leaves Gloria to work the coffee shop alone while he enjoys the parade on his break; Bill uses a trip to the hardware store to teach Remy a lesson in self-reliance.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707150000 +0000" stop="20250707153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>To impress her new friend, Tilly claims she saw stone gargoyles come to life; Cricket makes a deal to sell Bill's produce to a major grocery chain.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707153000 +0000" stop="20250707160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket uses his first tip from working at Big Coffee to buy a singing toy fish; Gramma kicks the family out of the house for the day, so they stay in a hotel for the first time.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707160000 +0000" stop="20250707163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma tells Cricket and Tilly that there's treasure buried on their property; Cricket adds his own doodles to Gloria's abstract paintings.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707163000 +0000" stop="20250707170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys decide to ramp up their local summer block party with supersized attractions; the kids work to save Mom after she is hit by Doof's inator.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707170000 +0000" stop="20250707173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The kids build a giant submarine sandwich submarine while Doof steals food; Candace tries to bust the boys while taking her driving test; Doof causes chaos in traffic.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707173000 +0000" stop="20250707180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace is turned into a fly.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707180000 +0000" stop="20250707183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Buford must keep Phineas and Ferb's invention from disappearing.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707183000 +0000" stop="20250707190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace is picked to be rutabaga princess.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707190000 +0000" stop="20250707193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>The Shuffle Battle Fest continues, and Multi's team, Multi and Me, goes up against Top Boyz.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707193000 +0000" stop="20250707200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny tries to keep a promise when the kids play with a strange diorama; Sara feels guilt after conning Larry out of his collectible beans.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707200000 +0000" stop="20250707203500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Larry must confront his jealousy or be consumed by it; to keep a secret, Lullah is forced to help Pliny assist a grub.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707203500 +0000" stop="20250707211000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>A spiraling Merian tries to figure out exactly why Francis left her party; the kids vie for a presidential sash.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707211000 +0000" stop="20250707214500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Merian tries to save Dr. Lullah's fish counter from a life of busy work; the kids put on a play to warn mutants about a disaster.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707214500 +0000" stop="20250707222000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Larry seeks to explore the island's nighttime entertainment; Chip aims to impress his rival by presenting himself as a formidable, apex predator worth hunting.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707222000 +0000" stop="20250707230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Sara lies in order to join the kids' Elephant Triumvirate book club; Larry asks Mr. Okay to help unlock the true power of his dud Zorb.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707230000 +0000" stop="20250707233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma assembles a seaworthy crew to retrieve packages stolen by Big City's porch pirates; Nick creates a fake scouting troop to trick Cricket and Tilly into raising money for him.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250707233000 +0000" stop="20250708000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff's thirst for life takes her on countless adventures through their city alongside her best friend, Barry.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-07</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708000000 +0000" stop="20250708003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Win or Lose</title>
    <desc>Laurie, the Coach's kid, struggles with insecurity that manifests into a creature only she can see.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708003000 +0000" stop="20250708010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Win or Lose</title>
    <desc>Blue, the umpire for the local softball league, surprises himself with newfound confidence when he tries a dating app.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708010000 +0000" stop="20250708013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Meap enlists Candace and the kids to help bust his nemesis, Mitch, before he can steal a long-lost treasure hidden somewhere on Earth.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708013000 +0000" stop="20250708020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill forces his family to embrace a live, laugh, love philosophy; Gloria tries to maintain her café's perfect rating.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708020000 +0000" stop="20250708023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket mentors a wild child; Tilly develops a cult following; Nancy tries to prove herself on the farm; Bill struggles to relax at a fancy spa with Gramma.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708023000 +0000" stop="20250708030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket is halted at a convenience store due to its no shoes, no service policy; when Remy throws Vasquez a surprise party, Bill's secret-keeping is put to the test.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708030000 +0000" stop="20250708033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly goes down an internet rabbit hole to figure out what happened to her favorite ice cream treat; Cricket tries to teach Gregly how to make friends.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708033000 +0000" stop="20250708040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill just wants Tilly to come down from a tree; when Remy tells Vasquez that he no longer needs his protection, Vasquez speaks with a therapist.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708040000 +0000" stop="20250708043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>A nature documentary portrays Big City as a wild ecosystem; avid collector Remy struggles to cope after Cricket finds the rarest of all trading cards.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708043000 +0000" stop="20250708050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>To prove to his parents that he is money-wise, Remy starts his own business; feeling neglected by his family, Bill befriends a murder of crows.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708050000 +0000" stop="20250708053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Young twins Dipper and Mabel Pines arrive to spend their summer break with their uncle.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708053000 +0000" stop="20250708060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>When Dipper and Mable hear rumors of a sea monster living in the lake, they want to prove it.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708060000 +0000" stop="20250708063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>When 14-year-old outcast Luz discovers a portal to a new world, she meets a witch named Eda and a demon named King; in order to get home, Luz has to help them with a mission.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708063000 +0000" stop="20250708070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>When an ancient wizard gives Luz a map for a mystical quest, she wonders if she is actually a Chosen One.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708070000 +0000" stop="20250708073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>LEAPIN LEGS! Merian is sent to a special place to learn how to relax. NICE TO PEAT YOU! Pliny dislodges a naturalist from a bog and joins him on a journey of discovery.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708073000 +0000" stop="20250708080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>CHLOROPHYLL-AINS! Francis has to protect a plant from a nefarious threat. EGGS-ISTENTIAL CRISIS! Merian struggles to open an egg salad stand with Pliny.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708080000 +0000" stop="20250708083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill forces his family to embrace a live, laugh, love philosophy; Gloria tries to maintain her café's perfect rating.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708083000 +0000" stop="20250708090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket mentors a wild child; Tilly develops a cult following; Nancy tries to prove herself on the farm; Bill struggles to relax at a fancy spa with Gramma.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708090000 +0000" stop="20250708093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket is halted at a convenience store due to its no shoes, no service policy; when Remy throws Vasquez a surprise party, Bill's secret-keeping is put to the test.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708093000 +0000" stop="20250708100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Bill set off on an epic journey to recycle a fluorescent light bulb at an e-waste center; Tilly tries to solve a long-standing feud between Gramma and Mr. Grigorian.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708100000 +0000" stop="20250708103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>On the trip to Big City movie multiplex, Cricket thinks he's too mature for a kids' movie, so he sneaks into a grown-up movie; Cricket registers his house on a home share website.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708103000 +0000" stop="20250708110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Cricket gets sick, his family steps in to fulfill his commitments for the day; the Green family's nemesis Chip Whistler shows up at the farmers' market in an attempt to steal business from them.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708110000 +0000" stop="20250708113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket invites the local news to see the huge watermelon Bill grew; Cricket stands up to the cyberbullying of three online gamers known as the Cyber Knights.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708113000 +0000" stop="20250708120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly takes Gramma out to be a tourist for a day; Cricket and Remy arrange a dinner party for everyone to get to know each other.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708120000 +0000" stop="20250708123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Big City faces a coffee bean shortage, Cricket and Gloria's boss, Ms. Cho, challenges them to retrieve one of the few remaining sacks of coffee; when the Greens' dog, Phoenix, runs away from home, the family sets out to find her.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708123000 +0000" stop="20250708130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket and Tilly's mother, Nancy Green, returns to the city.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708130000 +0000" stop="20250708133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Bill sneaks out at night with a mysterious duffel bag, the kids hide in his truck to see where he goes; Cricket impulsively buys a giant pet snake.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708133000 +0000" stop="20250708140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill and Nancy prep a special harvest dinner; Cricket and Gramma race Tilly to get a missing ingredient; at the local community center, Tilly wants to win a trophy and begins training with the center's director.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708140000 +0000" stop="20250708143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly tries ventriloquism for the Big Coffee open mic night; the family plays the people-watching game, making up stories about city folk passing by.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708143000 +0000" stop="20250708150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The Greens go on a family visit to the dentist's office, where Cricket is determined to avoid Dr. Enamel and power through his toothache.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708150000 +0000" stop="20250708153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Nancy's trailer is stolen by her old biker gang, the kids resolve to get it back; Cricket house-sits for Remy, but things go awry when the rest of the Greens visit.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708153000 +0000" stop="20250708160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>At the Valentine's Dance, Cricket develops an unwanted crush on Gabriella; Cricket joins forces with Officer Keys to hunt down a neighborhood litterbug.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708160000 +0000" stop="20250708163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma spurns Tilly at the city park, so Tilly tries making her jealous; Gramma makes special biscuits for the kids when they're hurt, but won't make more when they're better.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708163000 +0000" stop="20250708170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys build an endless ice luge to beat the heat while Doof brings oil to a waterpark; Candace and Doof see the same psychologist, who thinks their experiences may be connected.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708170000 +0000" stop="20250708173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys build a zoetrope that goes on an adventure of its own; the kids build a bookcase that gets attacked by an army of Doof-plants.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708173000 +0000" stop="20250708180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys make a giant inflatable wading pool for Mom; Isabella and the Fireside Girls attempt to get their Bee Keeping patch by turning themselves into bees.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708180000 +0000" stop="20250708183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Agent P teams up a human agent to stop a hijacked train.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708183000 +0000" stop="20250708190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace believes she will have an easy day; the boys ask her to get mom.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708190000 +0000" stop="20250708193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>The match between Team Multi and Me and Team Top Boyz enters its final battle.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708193000 +0000" stop="20250708200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Lullah wants alone time and creates a Manatee-Nanny to watch the kids; Pliny must choose - support Larry's noodling habit or keep him safe.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708200000 +0000" stop="20250708203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Young twins Dipper and Mabel Pines arrive to spend their summer break with their uncle.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708203000 +0000" stop="20250708210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>When Dipper and Mable hear rumors of a sea monster living in the lake, they want to prove it.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708210000 +0000" stop="20250708213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Dipper and Mabel set out to find out who tampered with Mabel's statue.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708213000 +0000" stop="20250708220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>When Dipper tries to impress Wendy by acting older than he really is, he's invited to join a group of teenagers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708220000 +0000" stop="20250708223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Dipper and Mabel find a new neighbor, a psychic kid named Lil' Gideon.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708223000 +0000" stop="20250708230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Dipper travels into the forest to battle Multi-Bear in a quest to attain manliness.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708230000 +0000" stop="20250708233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Dipper, wishing he could go back in time and undo a mistake he made, discovers a time machine.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250708233000 +0000" stop="20250709000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>The adventures of 12-year old twin brother and sister Dipper and Mabel Pines.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-08</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250709000000 +0000" stop="20250710000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Cricket wrestle with decision making at a truck stop between Big City and the country; Tilly rises through the ranks as a Big City jingle writer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-09</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
