<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv date="20250818090953 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403837/20250818.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403837&amp;date=20250818&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403837">
    <display-name lang="US">Disney XD USA - Eastern Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818000000 +0000" stop="20250818003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb spin the house in order to paint it more quickly.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818003000 +0000" stop="20250818010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>When the boys are mistaken as a super hero, a villain arrives in town to challenge them.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818010000 +0000" stop="20250818013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>When Irving's brother, Albert, calls Phineas and Ferb fakes, Buford and Baljeet pretend to be the boys so that Irving can prove Albert wrong; Candace runs a bust camp in her backyard to prep for busting Phineas and Ferb.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818013000 +0000" stop="20250818020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys' chameleon grows to a dinosaur's size; Phineas and Ferb put on a rodeo with robotic bulls.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818020000 +0000" stop="20250818023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Building an ATV; Creating the world's tallest building.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818023000 +0000" stop="20250818030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace becomes mayor for the day; ultimate lemonade stand.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818030000 +0000" stop="20250818033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys create a life sized maze filled with obstacles; Linda is asked to do a Lindana reunion concert.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818033000 +0000" stop="20250818040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>At the annual Comic Book Convention, Phineas and Ferb are caught in the middle of a duel between the fantasy fans and the sci-fi fans, and the boys must get them to set aside their differences so that they can get back to having fun.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818040000 +0000" stop="20250818043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip tries committing to the ways of survivalist Nils Vulfen; when the kids encounter a dolphin, everyone is excited - except Merian.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818043000 +0000" stop="20250818050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Lullah sends Sara to stop a rover from drawing a dirty rear on the moon; Francis goes on a quest to deliver a letter.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818050000 +0000" stop="20250818053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip is forced to use slap-based tactics to defend a bullied mutant; the kids prank accidentally lures one of Lullahs nemeses to the island.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818053000 +0000" stop="20250818060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny and the Kelp Folk try to beat Lullah at her own game; Mr. Okay worries Lullah is going to replace him.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818060000 +0000" stop="20250818063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>With Tater's Corner overrun by primos, Tater hunts for a hiding place to call her own; Nachito transfers his hero worship from Big Nacho to Tater.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818063000 +0000" stop="20250818070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater tracks down a mysterious masked skater; Tater tries to get invited to the T Sisters' gossip parties.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818070000 +0000" stop="20250818073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater's primos try to help her improve her Spanish with a homemade escape room; Tater introduces her littlest cousin to the library.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818073000 +0000" stop="20250818080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater tries to see into her own future; Tater teams up with the primos to get revenge on The Skid.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818080000 +0000" stop="20250818083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill promises his family a trip to the mall food court; when he reveals it was just a trick to get them to a family portrait studio, Cricket and Gramma try to escape; Remy is caught skipping his violin lessons to hang out with Cricket.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818083000 +0000" stop="20250818090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket Green and his family move from the country to Big City to live with Gramma; when Cricket and Bill accidentally disturb a nest of raccoons in the garage, they invade the house.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818090000 +0000" stop="20250818093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill takes Gramma to a doctor's checkup and leaves Tilly in charge of Cricket; Cricket learns that Bill never realized his childhood dream of becoming a gymnast.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818093000 +0000" stop="20250818100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill takes the family on a road trip to the country, only to wind up trapped in a traffic jam; when Tilly finds a bird's nest, she cares for the eggs hoping the chicks will think she's their mother, but the birds imprint on Cricket instead.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818100000 +0000" stop="20250818103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Bill learns that Gramma has been purposely creating a bad reputation around town, he throws a barbeque to befriend the neighbors; Cricket's scheme to cash in on a wishing well snares Tilly, leaving Cricket with a dilemma.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818103000 +0000" stop="20250818110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket earns a role in Big Coffee's new TV commercial but loses his confidence; Bill gets more than he bargained for when he trades in his pickup for a cutting-edge electric car.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818110000 +0000" stop="20250818113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When the Greens return Gramma and Remy to Big City, they are determined to delay their goodbyes for as long as possible.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818113000 +0000" stop="20250818120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The kids plan a heist to steal honey from Bill's beehive; Cricket and Remy run a campaign to get Phoenix, the dog, elected as mayor.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818120000 +0000" stop="20250818123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>A pizza delivery girl from Big City has to flee from a crazed country family; when Bill gets a horse for the day, Tilly must hide how much she secretly hates horses.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818123000 +0000" stop="20250818130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Brooke Dillman guest stars as diner owner Patti; Nancy tries to get Cricket to cut his new rat tail without admitting that she hates it.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818130000 +0000" stop="20250818133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>While Cricket shows Remy the fun of country life, Tilly seeks new sleeping arrangements; Cricket tries to win back his old country friend, Hector.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818133000 +0000" stop="20250818140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Remy determines to become a martial arts warrior after freezeing in the face of danger; Cricket's missing dirt jar prompts the story of when the Greens left their country farm.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818140000 +0000" stop="20250818143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill goes out of his way to get on a neighbor's good side; Cricket must prove himself worthy to avoid losing his delivery job to a robot.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818143000 +0000" stop="20250818150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Bill set off on an epic journey to recycle a fluorescent light bulb at an e-waste center; Tilly tries to solve a long-standing feud between Gramma and Mr. Grigorian.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818150000 +0000" stop="20250818153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket mentors a wild child; Tilly develops a cult following; Nancy tries to prove herself on the farm; Bill struggles to relax at a fancy spa with Gramma.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818153000 +0000" stop="20250818160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket discovers lake life brings out Bill's fun-loving side; when rabbits threaten to destroy Bill's crops, Nancy enlists their country friends to save the harvest.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818160000 +0000" stop="20250818163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Andromeda exchange letters that reveal their outlooks on the world; Remy enlists the Greens to help him lie to his parents about his week in the country.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818163000 +0000" stop="20250818170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb work to rescue the Lake Nose monster from the effects of zinc-free water after Dr. Doofenschmirtz removes all the metal from the water.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818170000 +0000" stop="20250818173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb invent an animal translator; the boys produce a huge concert event to raise awareness for the plastic thing at the end of shoelaces.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818173000 +0000" stop="20250818180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff has an unsneezed sneeze trapped in her head so she and Barry try everything to get it out; Kiff and Barry meet their favorite actor, but does he not like them?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818180000 +0000" stop="20250818183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff, Barry, and Trevor sneak into a movie and try not to get caught. Martin and Beryl vie for Kiff's favor when Kiff comes into some money.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818183000 +0000" stop="20250818190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and the gang get trapped in the aerial tram and try not to lose their minds; Kiff gets a haircut she hates.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818190000 +0000" stop="20250818193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>After their victory against Team Zooganic, Multi uses some Beycrafting skills to help Robin improve his game.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818193000 +0000" stop="20250818200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Kids face fears to retrieve lost ball as Lullah tricks them into devious game.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818200000 +0000" stop="20250818203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>A spiraling Merian tries to figure out exactly why Francis left her party; the kids vie for a presidential sash.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818203000 +0000" stop="20250818210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Larry must confront his jealousy or be consumed by it; to keep a secret, Lullah is forced to help Pliny assist a grub.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818210000 +0000" stop="20250818213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny and the Kelp Folk try to beat Lullah at her own game; Mr. Okay worries Lullah is going to replace him.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818213000 +0000" stop="20250818220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip is forced to use slap-based tactics to defend a bullied mutant; the kids prank accidentally lures one of Lullahs nemeses to the island.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818220000 +0000" stop="20250818223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip wants to make a breakfast that will blow his friends' socks off; Larry saves a baby lizard and swears to protect it from harm.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818223000 +0000" stop="20250818230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny tries to keep a promise when the kids play with a strange diorama; Sara feels guilt after conning Larry out of his collectible beans.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818230000 +0000" stop="20250818233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys build the world's greatest roller coaster; Candace is surprised during a trip to Mount Rushmore.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818233000 +0000" stop="20250819000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys enter the family automobile in a car race; then, a tropical beach paradise in the backyard goes awry.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819000000 +0000" stop="20250819003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candance finds a lava rock necklace and Phineas and Ferb ride some waves.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819003000 +0000" stop="20250819010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace is split into two Candaces; Phineas and Ferb make a sick day triathalon.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819010000 +0000" stop="20250819013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace switches places with a princess who looks just like her; Linda and Lawrence take a trip and they entrust Candace to be in charge of the house.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819013000 +0000" stop="20250819020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>In this musical, Phineas and Ferb revisit the day they built their gigantic rollercoaster.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819020000 +0000" stop="20250819023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys invent a pair of boots that make the wearer to be faster; the kids decide to create and race a giant hot air balloon.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819023000 +0000" stop="20250819030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb build a huge biodome; Candace pays a visit to Jeremy's house.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819030000 +0000" stop="20250819033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys make a mechanical version of a historical shark; the boys take some cows to the moon.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819033000 +0000" stop="20250819040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Ferb puts together a clip show of the gang's favorite moments in celebration of Phineas' birthday.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819040000 +0000" stop="20250819043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Big Tech unveils its slate of AI-generated TV shows based on the people of Big City; Tilly's belief in positive thinking is tested when she drives Lupita's faulty go-kart.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819043000 +0000" stop="20250819050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>A hungry Cricket finds a way to speed up a restaurant's short wait; Nancy tries to stop Cricket from breaking all of Smalton's weird laws.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819050000 +0000" stop="20250819053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>The Pines family resolves to get back to normal after the Lil' Gideon incident by throwing a party.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819053000 +0000" stop="20250819060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Dipper's secret journal pages lead him and the gang to the author's hidden bunker where they find themselves face-to-face with a mysterious figure from Gravity Falls' lore.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819060000 +0000" stop="20250819063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>When Amity Blight's parents get Luz, Willow and Gus expelled from Hexside, Luz strikes a dangerous deal with them to get back into school.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819063000 +0000" stop="20250819070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>King's delusions of grandeur lead Luz, Lilith and Hooty to a perilous new island.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819070000 +0000" stop="20250819073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>CHLOROPHYLL-AINS! Francis has to protect a plant from a nefarious threat. EGGS-ISTENTIAL CRISIS! Merian struggles to open an egg salad stand with Pliny.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819073000 +0000" stop="20250819080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>LEAPIN LEGS! Merian is sent to a special place to learn how to relax. NICE TO PEAT YOU! Pliny dislodges a naturalist from a bog and joins him on a journey of discovery.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819080000 +0000" stop="20250819083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket treats his family to dinner, but Bill is suspicious about how he plans to pay for it; Tilly and Cricket battle to see if Bill lies about liking their Father's Day gifts.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819083000 +0000" stop="20250819090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Remy's plan for his whole life is thrown into question when he is unprepared for a violin recital; Gramma becomes a rideshare driver, only to find her best customers are robbers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819090000 +0000" stop="20250819093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly searches the mall for a new look to reflect her maturity; Cricket persuades Bill to buy a farming robot to get out of chores.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819093000 +0000" stop="20250819100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Chip Whistler and Bill hit it off and become friends at Farm Con; Cricket stumbles into having 100 dollars and immediately buys into a pyramid scheme.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819100000 +0000" stop="20250819103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly makes changes to her country's coming-of-age ceremony and Gramma wants none of it; Cricket fast-tracks his training for a rodeo and gets trapped in a never-ending montage.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819103000 +0000" stop="20250819110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Remy attempts to find his country grit while Cricket takes tractor-driving lessons; Phoenix journeys back to Big City to retrieve Saxon while Gramma and Gloria go to a club.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819110000 +0000" stop="20250819113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The Greens leave Big City and move back to their country farm; however, they grow unsettled when things aren't quite how they remember.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819113000 +0000" stop="20250819120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket loses his hearing and keeps it a secret from Bill; the Greens go to a hipster drive-in movie, where Gloria proves her life is fun by taking the perfect SnapAGram photo.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819120000 +0000" stop="20250819123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket wants to prove to his family that he is not dumb during trivia night at the café; Tilly gets punished for the first time and decides to break bad.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819123000 +0000" stop="20250819130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket is halted at a convenience store due to its no shoes, no service policy; when Remy throws Vasquez a surprise party, Bill's secret-keeping is put to the test.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819130000 +0000" stop="20250819133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill forces his family to embrace a live, laugh, love philosophy; Gloria tries to maintain her café's perfect rating.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819133000 +0000" stop="20250819140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>To impress her new friend, Tilly claims she saw stone gargoyles come to life; Cricket makes a deal to sell Bill's produce to a major grocery chain.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819140000 +0000" stop="20250819143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket uses his first tip from working at Big Coffee to buy a singing toy fish; Gramma kicks the family out of the house for the day, so they stay in a hotel for the first time.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819143000 +0000" stop="20250819150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma tells Cricket and Tilly that there's treasure buried on their property; Cricket adds his own doodles to Gloria's abstract paintings.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819150000 +0000" stop="20250819153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>On the trip to Big City movie multiplex, Cricket thinks he's too mature for a kids' movie, so he sneaks into a grown-up movie; Cricket registers his house on a home share website.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819153000 +0000" stop="20250819160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Cricket gets sick, his family steps in to fulfill his commitments for the day; the Green family's nemesis Chip Whistler shows up at the farmers' market in an attempt to steal business from them.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819160000 +0000" stop="20250819163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket invites the local news to see the huge watermelon Bill grew; Cricket stands up to the cyberbullying of three online gamers known as the Cyber Knights.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819163000 +0000" stop="20250819170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb care for an egg they believe belongs to Perry; the boys create their own video game starring themselves.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819170000 +0000" stop="20250819173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys accidentally knock an alien space craft while playing baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819173000 +0000" stop="20250819180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry accidentally cause a townwide blackout by upsetting a Lighthouse Keeper. Kiff has dinner at the Buns's and has to hide that she hates the food.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819180000 +0000" stop="20250819183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff runs for class president against a surprise candidate, Mr. RiPeppa. The Chatterleys take Barry on their island vacation, but he seems to have a dark secret.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819183000 +0000" stop="20250819190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry try to stay awake until 4am to see a very special comet. Kiff meets a bad banana.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819190000 +0000" stop="20250819193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>Team Phalanx is hanging on to their sponsorship by a thread, with their upcoming match with Team Persona their last chance to stay in the limelight.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819193000 +0000" stop="20250819200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Midnight Mutiny; Larry wants to see what the island's nightlife has to offer; Chip mods his bod; Chip wants his rival to see him as a tough, apex predator worthy of being hunted.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819200000 +0000" stop="20250819203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater's plans are foiled by her mom's insistence that she be a "Helpful Humphrey" to the primos; Tater discovers the perfect primo-repellant in Lot Lot's creepy doll.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819203000 +0000" stop="20250819210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater is thrilled to get her very first zit; Tater shadows her cool cousin Lita as she goes about her three jobs.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819210000 +0000" stop="20250819213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater tracks down a mysterious masked skater; Tater tries to get invited to the T Sisters' gossip parties.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819213000 +0000" stop="20250819223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater tries to see into her own future; Tater teams up with the primos to get revenge on The Skid.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819223000 +0000" stop="20250819230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater helps Toñita hide a secret from Tere and Tabi; Tater tries to host a sleepover while hiding the cousins.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819230000 +0000" stop="20250819233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb herd stampeding cattle back to a carnival; the boys create a winter wonderland in the middle of summer.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819233000 +0000" stop="20250820000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Stepbrothers keep busy during their summer vacation.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820000000 +0000" stop="20250821000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace discovers that Phineas and Ferb have invented a computer that can answer anything; Candace takes Perry to the Charity Pet Wash with her.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
