<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv date="20250817091035 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403837/20250817.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403837&amp;date=20250817&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403837">
    <display-name lang="US">Disney XD USA - Eastern Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817000000 +0000" stop="20250817003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb give Candace a makeover; Candace hopes to join the Fireside Girls before the Paisley Sideburn Brothers perform.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817003000 +0000" stop="20250817010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Dad accidentally sells Candace's favorite doll at a yard sale; after Baljeet saves him, Buford vows to become Baljeet's slave.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817010000 +0000" stop="20250817013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace blames the boys for an abandoned device; while at the beach, the boys and other neighborhood children locate the city of Atlantis.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817013000 +0000" stop="20250817020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys invent a transporter to retrieve any object; Candace convinces Jeremy to be her dancing partner for a hit TV show.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817020000 +0000" stop="20250817023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace wants to win the father-daughter obstacle course; Candace baby-sits for Jeremy's little sister.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817023000 +0000" stop="20250817030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Carl intercepts blueprints for an anti-gravity fun launcher; the boys encourage the neighborhood children to build customized floats.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817030000 +0000" stop="20250817033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys create an orb that allows them to pass through solid objects; Candace is excited to be the Maid of Honor at her aunt's wedding.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817033000 +0000" stop="20250817040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace becomes convinced that Ferb is an alien; Phineas and Ferb trick out the kiddie rides at the grocery store.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817040000 +0000" stop="20250817043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Stan is cursed by a witch; Mabel braves Claymotion; Waddles eats a bowl of jelly and builds a machine that allows him to speak.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817043000 +0000" stop="20250817050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>The kids, along with Old Man McGucket's help, discover there is a secret society in Gravity Falls.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817050000 +0000" stop="20250817053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Blendin Blandin returns to face off with Dipper and Mabel.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817053000 +0000" stop="20250817060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Mabel takes matchmaking too far when she steals a love potion from a real love god.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817060000 +0000" stop="20250817063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Pacifica enlists Dipper's help to rid the Northwest Mansion of a ghost.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817063000 +0000" stop="20250817070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>It's Palisman Pairing Day at Hexside; Luz doesn't match with a Palisman of her own and soon she finds herself on an unexpected journey with a foe.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817070000 +0000" stop="20250817073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>A person from Eda's past enlists her in a rebellion against the Emperor.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817073000 +0000" stop="20250817080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>Hooty tries to help King, Eda and Luz with their problems, but it doesn't go as planned.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817080000 +0000" stop="20250817083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>When Luz gets sick with the Common Mold, it's up to Amity to find an important ingredient for the portal door, but Amity's not the only one on its trail.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817083000 +0000" stop="20250817090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>Luz thinks she's found a way back home, but she may not be ready for what awaits on the other side.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817090000 +0000" stop="20250817093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket leaves Gloria to work the coffee shop alone while he enjoys the parade on his break; Bill uses a trip to the hardware store to teach Remy a lesson in self-reliance.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817093000 +0000" stop="20250817100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>While dining at a seafood restaurant, Bill feels he must prove to the waiter that he is a Big City local, and Cricket and Tilly try to rescue a live octopus; when Cricket loses all of his critterballs over the fence, Gloria refuses to return them.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817100000 +0000" stop="20250817103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Chip enacts his ultimate revenge plan by framing the Green family for ruining Big City and turning everyone against them.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817103000 +0000" stop="20250817110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Tilly sees a manipulative ad, she goes to extremes to save all moths; after spending a week with Bill, Cricket fears he's infected with Billness.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817110000 +0000" stop="20250817113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Bakugan</title>
    <desc>Juno's injury leaves her unable to brawl in the tournament; Trox is invited by a talent agent to audition for a commercial for his favorite energy drink.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817113000 +0000" stop="20250817120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Yu-Gi-Oh! GO RUSH!!</title>
    <desc>Yudias must Rush Duel against a supersecret organization.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817120000 +0000" stop="20250817123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>Takumi's visit to Yggdrasil is interrupted by Karla parachuting in to greet Blaze; meanwhile, Multi looks for inspiration over lunch with Sigrid.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817123000 +0000" stop="20250817130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Merian tries to save Dr. Lullah's fish counter from a life of busy work; the kids put on a play to warn mutants about a disaster.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817130000 +0000" stop="20250817133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Kids face fears to retrieve lost ball as Lullah tricks them into devious game.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817133000 +0000" stop="20250817140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry accompany Trollie on a mission to his magical neighborhood; the Chatterley family heads to Okaywill for new winter coats.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817140000 +0000" stop="20250817143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Trevor becomes the foundation of the newest Table Town School craze, but at what cost? Kiff, Barry and Terri go to the Table Town Mall, but get caught up in a long line.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817143000 +0000" stop="20250817150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater makes a mixtape to document her summer; Tater learns how to act more mature from Serena while teaching Serena how to act more like a kid.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817150000 +0000" stop="20250817153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater tries to fit in at a local festival celebrating Latinidad; Tater tries to help Tere and Tonita show their big sis Tabi how much they appreciate her.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817153000 +0000" stop="20250817160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys build a zoetrope that goes on an adventure of its own; the kids build a bookcase that gets attacked by an army of Doof-plants.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817160000 +0000" stop="20250817163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys bring Perry to the vet for a checkup and build a pet wash while they wait; Carl tries to help Perry stop Doof while working three other part-time jobs.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817163000 +0000" stop="20250817170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The Flynn-Fletchers take a cruise; Doof steals shrunken goods; Isabella struggles to lead the Fireside Girls on her own, while Doof renews his evil business license.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817170000 +0000" stop="20250817173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>The kids get sucked into a white-hot, Mutant soap opera; Sara attempts to nail the perfect hairstyle so she can be the star of Francis' painting.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817173000 +0000" stop="20250817180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Merian takes on the case of a destructive space chimp; Pliny wants to play Geoplomacy when the kids discover six sandbars.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817180000 +0000" stop="20250817183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip becomes a spy to prove he's not a nincompoop; after a close call, daredevil Larry embraces a life of extreme caution.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817183000 +0000" stop="20250817190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Sara lies in order to join the kids' Elephant Triumvirate book club; Larry asks Mr. Okay to help unlock the true power of his dud Zorb.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817190000 +0000" stop="20250817193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff's thirst for life takes her on countless adventures through their city alongside her best friend, Barry.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817193000 +0000" stop="20250817200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>A trip to the aquarium! Kiff worries that she's annoying.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817200000 +0000" stop="20250817203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry try to stay awake until 4am to see a very special comet. Kiff meets a bad banana.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817203000 +0000" stop="20250817210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff goes on a ski trip with Reggie's family; Trevor can't play the piano and needs Kiff and Barry's help.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817210000 +0000" stop="20250817213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater uncovers a disturbing secret about her hometown; she celebrates her first double-digit birthday.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817213000 +0000" stop="20250817223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater is finally old enough to join the older primos' tabletop roleplaying game; Tater tries to help fix Lita's strained relationship with her mom.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817223000 +0000" stop="20250817230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater tries not to interfere in Nachito's big errand; Tater celebrates her favorite summer family holiday.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817230000 +0000" stop="20250817233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Vanessa and Doof travel to Drusselstein while the boys dig for Mom's lost wedding ring; The kids build a bird mansion for a rare macaw while Doof deals with giant praying mantises.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250817233000 +0000" stop="20250818000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Doof's dream-project-inator misfires and projects people's dreams for all to see; Doof becomes the center of his own solar system while Irving tries to impress Phineas and Ferb.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-17</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818000000 +0000" stop="20250818003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb spin the house in order to paint it more quickly.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818003000 +0000" stop="20250818010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>When the boys are mistaken as a super hero, a villain arrives in town to challenge them.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818010000 +0000" stop="20250818013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>When Irving's brother, Albert, calls Phineas and Ferb fakes, Buford and Baljeet pretend to be the boys so that Irving can prove Albert wrong; Candace runs a bust camp in her backyard to prep for busting Phineas and Ferb.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818013000 +0000" stop="20250818020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys' chameleon grows to a dinosaur's size; Phineas and Ferb put on a rodeo with robotic bulls.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818020000 +0000" stop="20250818023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Building an ATV; Creating the world's tallest building.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818023000 +0000" stop="20250818030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace becomes mayor for the day; ultimate lemonade stand.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818030000 +0000" stop="20250818033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys create a life sized maze filled with obstacles; Linda is asked to do a Lindana reunion concert.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818033000 +0000" stop="20250818040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>At the annual Comic Book Convention, Phineas and Ferb are caught in the middle of a duel between the fantasy fans and the sci-fi fans, and the boys must get them to set aside their differences so that they can get back to having fun.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818040000 +0000" stop="20250818043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip tries committing to the ways of survivalist Nils Vulfen; when the kids encounter a dolphin, everyone is excited - except Merian.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818043000 +0000" stop="20250818050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Lullah sends Sara to stop a rover from drawing a dirty rear on the moon; Francis goes on a quest to deliver a letter.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818050000 +0000" stop="20250818053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip is forced to use slap-based tactics to defend a bullied mutant; the kids prank accidentally lures one of Lullahs nemeses to the island.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818053000 +0000" stop="20250818060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny and the Kelp Folk try to beat Lullah at her own game; Mr. Okay worries Lullah is going to replace him.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818060000 +0000" stop="20250818063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>With Tater's Corner overrun by primos, Tater hunts for a hiding place to call her own; Nachito transfers his hero worship from Big Nacho to Tater.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818063000 +0000" stop="20250818070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater tracks down a mysterious masked skater; Tater tries to get invited to the T Sisters' gossip parties.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818070000 +0000" stop="20250818073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater's primos try to help her improve her Spanish with a homemade escape room; Tater introduces her littlest cousin to the library.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818073000 +0000" stop="20250818080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater tries to see into her own future; Tater teams up with the primos to get revenge on The Skid.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818080000 +0000" stop="20250818083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill promises his family a trip to the mall food court; when he reveals it was just a trick to get them to a family portrait studio, Cricket and Gramma try to escape; Remy is caught skipping his violin lessons to hang out with Cricket.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818083000 +0000" stop="20250818090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket Green and his family move from the country to Big City to live with Gramma; when Cricket and Bill accidentally disturb a nest of raccoons in the garage, they invade the house.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818090000 +0000" stop="20250818093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill takes Gramma to a doctor's checkup and leaves Tilly in charge of Cricket; Cricket learns that Bill never realized his childhood dream of becoming a gymnast.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818093000 +0000" stop="20250818100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill takes the family on a road trip to the country, only to wind up trapped in a traffic jam; when Tilly finds a bird's nest, she cares for the eggs hoping the chicks will think she's their mother, but the birds imprint on Cricket instead.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818100000 +0000" stop="20250818103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Bill learns that Gramma has been purposely creating a bad reputation around town, he throws a barbeque to befriend the neighbors; Cricket's scheme to cash in on a wishing well snares Tilly, leaving Cricket with a dilemma.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818103000 +0000" stop="20250818110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket earns a role in Big Coffee's new TV commercial but loses his confidence; Bill gets more than he bargained for when he trades in his pickup for a cutting-edge electric car.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818110000 +0000" stop="20250818113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When the Greens return Gramma and Remy to Big City, they are determined to delay their goodbyes for as long as possible.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818113000 +0000" stop="20250818120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The kids plan a heist to steal honey from Bill's beehive; Cricket and Remy run a campaign to get Phoenix, the dog, elected as mayor.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818120000 +0000" stop="20250818123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>A pizza delivery girl from Big City has to flee from a crazed country family; when Bill gets a horse for the day, Tilly must hide how much she secretly hates horses.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818123000 +0000" stop="20250818130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Brooke Dillman guest stars as diner owner Patti; Nancy tries to get Cricket to cut his new rat tail without admitting that she hates it.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818130000 +0000" stop="20250818133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>While Cricket shows Remy the fun of country life, Tilly seeks new sleeping arrangements; Cricket tries to win back his old country friend, Hector.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818133000 +0000" stop="20250818140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Remy determines to become a martial arts warrior after freezeing in the face of danger; Cricket's missing dirt jar prompts the story of when the Greens left their country farm.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818140000 +0000" stop="20250818143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill goes out of his way to get on a neighbor's good side; Cricket must prove himself worthy to avoid losing his delivery job to a robot.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818143000 +0000" stop="20250818150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Bill set off on an epic journey to recycle a fluorescent light bulb at an e-waste center; Tilly tries to solve a long-standing feud between Gramma and Mr. Grigorian.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818150000 +0000" stop="20250818153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket mentors a wild child; Tilly develops a cult following; Nancy tries to prove herself on the farm; Bill struggles to relax at a fancy spa with Gramma.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818153000 +0000" stop="20250818160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket discovers lake life brings out Bill's fun-loving side; when rabbits threaten to destroy Bill's crops, Nancy enlists their country friends to save the harvest.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818160000 +0000" stop="20250818163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Andromeda exchange letters that reveal their outlooks on the world; Remy enlists the Greens to help him lie to his parents about his week in the country.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818163000 +0000" stop="20250818170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb work to rescue the Lake Nose monster from the effects of zinc-free water after Dr. Doofenschmirtz removes all the metal from the water.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818170000 +0000" stop="20250818173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb invent an animal translator; the boys produce a huge concert event to raise awareness for the plastic thing at the end of shoelaces.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818173000 +0000" stop="20250818180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff has an unsneezed sneeze trapped in her head so she and Barry try everything to get it out; Kiff and Barry meet their favorite actor, but does he not like them?</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818180000 +0000" stop="20250818183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff, Barry, and Trevor sneak into a movie and try not to get caught. Martin and Beryl vie for Kiff's favor when Kiff comes into some money.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818183000 +0000" stop="20250818190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and the gang get trapped in the aerial tram and try not to lose their minds; Kiff gets a haircut she hates.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818190000 +0000" stop="20250818193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>After their victory against Team Zooganic, Multi uses some Beycrafting skills to help Robin improve his game.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818193000 +0000" stop="20250818200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Kids face fears to retrieve lost ball as Lullah tricks them into devious game.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818200000 +0000" stop="20250818203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>A spiraling Merian tries to figure out exactly why Francis left her party; the kids vie for a presidential sash.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818203000 +0000" stop="20250818210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Larry must confront his jealousy or be consumed by it; to keep a secret, Lullah is forced to help Pliny assist a grub.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818210000 +0000" stop="20250818213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny and the Kelp Folk try to beat Lullah at her own game; Mr. Okay worries Lullah is going to replace him.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818213000 +0000" stop="20250818220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip is forced to use slap-based tactics to defend a bullied mutant; the kids prank accidentally lures one of Lullahs nemeses to the island.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818220000 +0000" stop="20250818223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip wants to make a breakfast that will blow his friends' socks off; Larry saves a baby lizard and swears to protect it from harm.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818223000 +0000" stop="20250818230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny tries to keep a promise when the kids play with a strange diorama; Sara feels guilt after conning Larry out of his collectible beans.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818230000 +0000" stop="20250818233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys build the world's greatest roller coaster; Candace is surprised during a trip to Mount Rushmore.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250818233000 +0000" stop="20250819000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys enter the family automobile in a car race; then, a tropical beach paradise in the backyard goes awry.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-18</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819000000 +0000" stop="20250820000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candance finds a lava rock necklace and Phineas and Ferb ride some waves.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
