<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv date="20250722090855 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403837/20250722.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403837&amp;date=20250722&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403837">
    <display-name lang="US">Disney XD USA - Eastern Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722000000 +0000" stop="20250722003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Win or Lose</title>
    <desc>Bored at sister Taylor's softball games, imaginative Ira befriends mischievous teens.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722003000 +0000" stop="20250722012000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Win or Lose</title>
    <desc>Yuwen, a pitcher of the softball team, loves to be the center of attention; he's in conflict with Little Yuwen, his vulnerable self who shows up in Yuwen's mind; his relationship with his girlfriend and the entire championship game are at stake.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722012000 +0000" stop="20250722013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chibiverse</title>
    <desc>A new island is created; Marcy unleashes a magic potion; Grunkle Stan puts together a heist.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722013000 +0000" stop="20250722020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket loses his hearing and keeps it a secret from Bill; the Greens go to a hipster drive-in movie, where Gloria proves her life is fun by taking the perfect SnapAGram photo.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722020000 +0000" stop="20250722023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Remy determines to become a martial arts warrior after freezeing in the face of danger; Cricket's missing dirt jar prompts the story of when the Greens left their country farm.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722023000 +0000" stop="20250722030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The Greens leave Big City and move back to their country farm; however, they grow unsettled when things aren't quite how they remember.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722030000 +0000" stop="20250722033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill forces his family to embrace a live, laugh, love philosophy; Gloria tries to maintain her café's perfect rating.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722033000 +0000" stop="20250722040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket mentors a wild child; Tilly develops a cult following; Nancy tries to prove herself on the farm; Bill struggles to relax at a fancy spa with Gramma.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722040000 +0000" stop="20250722043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket is halted at a convenience store due to its no shoes, no service policy; when Remy throws Vasquez a surprise party, Bill's secret-keeping is put to the test.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722043000 +0000" stop="20250722050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Bill set off on an epic journey to recycle a fluorescent light bulb at an e-waste center; Tilly tries to solve a long-standing feud between Gramma and Mr. Grigorian.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722050000 +0000" stop="20250722053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>When Lil' Gideon takes over the Shack, Dipper and Mabel try to defeat him.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722053000 +0000" stop="20250722060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>The Pines family resolves to get back to normal after the Lil' Gideon incident by throwing a party.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722060000 +0000" stop="20250722063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>When Amity Blight's parents get Luz, Willow and Gus expelled from Hexside, Luz strikes a dangerous deal with them to get back into school.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722063000 +0000" stop="20250722070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>King's delusions of grandeur lead Luz, Lilith and Hooty to a perilous new island.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722070000 +0000" stop="20250722073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>LEAPIN LEGS! Merian is sent to a special place to learn how to relax. NICE TO PEAT YOU! Pliny dislodges a naturalist from a bog and joins him on a journey of discovery.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722073000 +0000" stop="20250722080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>The kids get sucked into a white-hot, Mutant soap opera; Sara attempts to nail the perfect hairstyle so she can be the star of Francis' painting.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722080000 +0000" stop="20250722083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Big City faces a coffee bean shortage, Cricket and Gloria's boss, Ms. Cho, challenges them to retrieve one of the few remaining sacks of coffee; when the Greens' dog, Phoenix, runs away from home, the family sets out to find her.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722083000 +0000" stop="20250722090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket and Tilly's mother, Nancy Green, returns to the city.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250722090000 +0000" stop="20250723000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Bill sneaks out at night with a mysterious duffel bag, the kids hide in his truck to see where he goes; Cricket impulsively buys a giant pet snake.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-22</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
