<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv date="20250812090416 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403837/20250812.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403837&amp;date=20250812&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403837">
    <display-name lang="US">Disney XD USA - Eastern Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812000000 +0000" stop="20250812003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys build the world's greatest roller coaster; Candace is surprised during a trip to Mount Rushmore.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812003000 +0000" stop="20250812010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys enter the family automobile in a car race; then, a tropical beach paradise in the backyard goes awry.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812010000 +0000" stop="20250812013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb herd stampeding cattle back to a carnival; the boys create a winter wonderland in the middle of summer.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812013000 +0000" stop="20250812020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys capture Candace, who is wrapped up like a mummy; Phineas and the Ferb-Tones become a one-hit wonder.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812020000 +0000" stop="20250812023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas enters a thumb-wrestling contest with Buford; Candace tries out for the lead in her favorite play.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812023000 +0000" stop="20250812030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys scare Candace with a fake Bigfoot; Phineas and Ferb create treehouses for themselves and Candace.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812030000 +0000" stop="20250812033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Dr. Doofenshmirtz makes Perry the Platypus jealous with his new nemesis; Phineas and Ferb travel back in time.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812033000 +0000" stop="20250812040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb create a circus for the neighborhood; the boys market a wooden toy version of Perry the platypus.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812040000 +0000" stop="20250812043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket gets dumped by his girlfriend, so he tries to change to win her back; Bill becomes hyper-competitive when Cricket starts to be better at things than him.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812043000 +0000" stop="20250812050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The mischievous Cricket Green and his family pick up their lives in the country to start anew in the big city.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812050000 +0000" stop="20250812053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Dipper is self-conscious that Mabel is taller than him so he seeks out a magic way to grow himself.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812053000 +0000" stop="20250812060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Dipper and Mabel are excited to join in on the fun, but when Wendy casually mentions that trick-or-treating is for kids, Dipper's whole outlook on the evening changes.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812060000 +0000" stop="20250812063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>King finally becomes a successful author by writing a bestseller; his books fly off the shelves, but then he finds out that he should have read the small print.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812063000 +0000" stop="20250812070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>Luz needs to learn a new spell, so Eda trains her in a magical place on the island.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812070000 +0000" stop="20250812073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Sweet summer science; the kids arrive at Lullah's mysterious summer camp and attempt to fix her laser; mutant mischief; the kids must face the Mutant thieves who stole their food.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812073000 +0000" stop="20250812080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny tries to keep a promise when the kids play with a strange diorama; Sara feels guilt after conning Larry out of his collectible beans.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812080000 +0000" stop="20250812083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>To impress her new friend, Tilly claims she saw stone gargoyles come to life; Cricket makes a deal to sell Bill's produce to a major grocery chain.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812083000 +0000" stop="20250812090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket uses his first tip from working at Big Coffee to buy a singing toy fish; Gramma kicks the family out of the house for the day, so they stay in a hotel for the first time.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812090000 +0000" stop="20250812093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma tells Cricket and Tilly that there's treasure buried on their property; Cricket adds his own doodles to Gloria's abstract paintings.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812093000 +0000" stop="20250812100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>On the trip to Big City movie multiplex, Cricket thinks he's too mature for a kids' movie, so he sneaks into a grown-up movie; Cricket registers his house on a home share website.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812100000 +0000" stop="20250812103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>After being mocked for his handshake, Cricket trains for a Western-style handshake duel; Gloria combines her work life and social life by hiring her friends as employees.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812103000 +0000" stop="20250812110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma butts heads with Nick when he crashes her special family hockey outing; Chip Whistler recounts what happened to him since "Chipocalypse Now.".</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812110000 +0000" stop="20250812113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly goes down an internet rabbit hole to figure out what happened to her favorite ice cream treat; Cricket tries to teach Gregly how to make friends.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812113000 +0000" stop="20250812120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill just wants Tilly to come down from a tree; when Remy tells Vasquez that he no longer needs his protection, Vasquez speaks with a therapist.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812120000 +0000" stop="20250812123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>A nature documentary portrays Big City as a wild ecosystem; avid collector Remy struggles to cope after Cricket finds the rarest of all trading cards.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812123000 +0000" stop="20250812130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>To prove to his parents that he is money-wise, Remy starts his own business; feeling neglected by his family, Bill befriends a murder of crows.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812130000 +0000" stop="20250812133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket tries to avoid a fortune teller's ominous prediction that he will get a stinky slap; in an inescapable escape room, Cricket must decide between family and freedom.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812133000 +0000" stop="20250812140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket is caught eating dog food by Gloria and must stop her from revealing his secret shame; Bill installs a parenting device to monitor and discipline Cricket for him.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812140000 +0000" stop="20250812143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill receives a surprise; Jade's boss suspends her from work.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812143000 +0000" stop="20250812150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket tries to come up with the perfect prank to play on his girlfriend on April Fool's Day; Bill goes to extremes to prevent Tilly from experiencing grief.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812150000 +0000" stop="20250812153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Chip Whistler attempts to create an evil family, so he takes down the Greens; the Greens move to the suburbs and live under new identities to hide from Chip.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812153000 +0000" stop="20250812160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The Greens cause trouble during free sample day at the Farmers Market; Cricket and Nancy toilet paper all of Smalton in a quest for pranking glory.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812160000 +0000" stop="20250812163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>In summer, Cricket impulsively eats Bill's chocolate Santa and must replace it; when Gramma's serene country retreat is disrupted by an outdoor festival, she resolves to stop it.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812163000 +0000" stop="20250812170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>The kids get sucked into a white-hot, Mutant soap opera; Sara attempts to nail the perfect hairstyle so she can be the star of Francis' painting.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812170000 +0000" stop="20250812173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Merian takes on the case of a destructive space chimp; Pliny wants to play Geoplomacy when the kids discover six sandbars.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812173000 +0000" stop="20250812180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip becomes a spy to prove he's not a nincompoop; after a close call, daredevil Larry embraces a life of extreme caution.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812180000 +0000" stop="20250812183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Sara lies in order to join the kids' Elephant Triumvirate book club; Larry asks Mr. Okay to help unlock the true power of his dud Zorb.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812183000 +0000" stop="20250812190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>A Mutant trio sets out to discover the purpose of some weird-shaped berries; a new visitor offers the kids the summer of their dreams.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812190000 +0000" stop="20250812193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>Now that Team Persona is officially sponsored by Komaba Sushi, the team is finally ready to battle at The X.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812193000 +0000" stop="20250812200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chibiverse</title>
    <desc>Everyone's favorite squirrel, Kiff, hosts a game show.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812200000 +0000" stop="20250812203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry try to stay awake until 4am to see a very special comet. Kiff meets a bad banana.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812203000 +0000" stop="20250812210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>The Chatterleys get ready; Kiff and the crew run the morning announcements at school and it gets out of control.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812210000 +0000" stop="20250812213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and the crew learn magic, but end up in over their heads; Helen casts a spell on Kiff and Barry and won't tell them what it is.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812213000 +0000" stop="20250812220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry pick up trash in the park but can't decide what is trash; Trevor works out his frustrations by writing libelous stories about Kiff and Barry.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812220000 +0000" stop="20250812223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff's good deed goes unnoticed while Reggie's receives lots of attention; Kiff and Barry enjoy a kids-only dinner with their shy classmate Darryn.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812223000 +0000" stop="20250812230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff's thirst for life takes her on countless adventures through their city alongside her best friend, Barry.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812230000 +0000" stop="20250812233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys build an endless ice luge to beat the heat while Doof brings oil to a waterpark; Candace and Doof see the same psychologist, who thinks their experiences may be connected.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812233000 +0000" stop="20250813000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys build a zoetrope that goes on an adventure of its own; the kids build a bookcase that gets attacked by an army of Doof-plants.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813000000 +0000" stop="20250813003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace joins a jousting tournament at the Renaissance festival; the boys build robot clones of themselves to complete more projects.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813003000 +0000" stop="20250813010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys undermine Candace's birthday gift for their mother; a shrinking sub excursion into Isabella's dog ends up in Candace.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813010000 +0000" stop="20250813013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace models clothing created by Phineas and Ferb; the boys cheer up Isabella after her tonsils are taken out.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813013000 +0000" stop="20250813020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys create a monster truck for Candace to practice her driving skills; Grandpa tells the boys about Badbeard the pirate while on a camping trip.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813020000 +0000" stop="20250813023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>When Dad forgets his wedding anniversary, the children must find their parents' favorite band; Dr. Doofenshmirtz plans a birthday party for his daughter.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813023000 +0000" stop="20250813030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb stumble upon Perry's secret lair; the boys help their grandfather jump a gorge on his motorcycle.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813030000 +0000" stop="20250813033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb get shipped off to reform school; investigative talk show host Morty Williams prepares an eye-opening report on the school.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813033000 +0000" stop="20250813040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb re-create a chariot race; a reality show records the brothers building a white-water rafting ride.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813040000 +0000" stop="20250813043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Chip enacts his ultimate revenge plan by framing the Green family for ruining Big City and turning everyone against them.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813043000 +0000" stop="20250813050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Tilly sees a manipulative ad, she goes to extremes to save all moths; after spending a week with Bill, Cricket fears he's infected with Billness.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813050000 +0000" stop="20250813053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>When Mabel questions the way Stan runs the Shack, he challenges her to a bet.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813053000 +0000" stop="20250813060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>While Stan, Dipper, Mabel and Soos are falling in a bottomless pit, they tell stories to pass time.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813060000 +0000" stop="20250813063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>Luz is thrilled on her first day of Magic School, but when she's told she can only study one type of magic, she can't choose between all the cool tracks.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813063000 +0000" stop="20250813070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>King confides in a carnival fortuneteller who makes his dream come true, but it comes at a cost.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813070000 +0000" stop="20250813073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip wants to make a breakfast that will blow his friends' socks off; Larry saves a baby lizard and swears to protect it from harm.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813073000 +0000" stop="20250813080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Lullah wants alone time and creates a Manatee-Nanny to watch the kids; Pliny must choose - support Larry's noodling habit or keep him safe.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813080000 +0000" stop="20250813083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Cricket gets sick, his family steps in to fulfill his commitments for the day; the Green family's nemesis Chip Whistler shows up at the farmers' market in an attempt to steal business from them.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813083000 +0000" stop="20250813090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket invites the local news to see the huge watermelon Bill grew; Cricket stands up to the cyberbullying of three online gamers known as the Cyber Knights.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813090000 +0000" stop="20250813093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly takes Gramma out to be a tourist for a day; Cricket and Remy arrange a dinner party for everyone to get to know each other.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813093000 +0000" stop="20250813100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Big City faces a coffee bean shortage, Cricket and Gloria's boss, Ms. Cho, challenges them to retrieve one of the few remaining sacks of coffee; when the Greens' dog, Phoenix, runs away from home, the family sets out to find her.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813100000 +0000" stop="20250813103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket gets dumped by his girlfriend, so he tries to change to win her back; Bill becomes hyper-competitive when Cricket starts to be better at things than him.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813103000 +0000" stop="20250813110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The mischievous Cricket Green and his family pick up their lives in the country to start anew in the big city.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813110000 +0000" stop="20250813113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Chip enacts his ultimate revenge plan by framing the Green family for ruining Big City and turning everyone against them.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813113000 +0000" stop="20250813120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Tilly sees a manipulative ad, she goes to extremes to save all moths; after spending a week with Bill, Cricket fears he's infected with Billness.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813120000 +0000" stop="20250813123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Identity crises abound; Wayne wants city excitement.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813123000 +0000" stop="20250813130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Saxon finds love; Remy's parents bond with him.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813130000 +0000" stop="20250813133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma assembles a seaworthy crew to retrieve packages stolen by Big City's porch pirates; Nick creates a fake scouting troop to trick Cricket and Tilly into raising money for him.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813133000 +0000" stop="20250813140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The Greens get the work out of their life at Big Citys new gym; cricket finds a loophole to his curfew that will let him attend a late-night drone show.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813140000 +0000" stop="20250813143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Big Tech unveils its slate of AI-generated TV shows based on the people of Big City; Tilly's belief in positive thinking is tested when she drives Lupita's faulty go-kart.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813143000 +0000" stop="20250813150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>A hungry Cricket finds a way to speed up a restaurant's short wait; Nancy tries to stop Cricket from breaking all of Smalton's weird laws.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813150000 +0000" stop="20250813153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly tries to inspire others into community improvement by cleaning up dog droppings; Nick suggests Nancy start a U-Pick operation, but Nancy remains suspicious of his intentions.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813153000 +0000" stop="20250813160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket and Remy recall an adventure at the museum that almost derailed their friendship; Cricket learns he was unexpected.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813160000 +0000" stop="20250813163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly revives Cousin Jilly, an alter-ego she created to entertain Cricket when they were younger; Gloria opens a secret café in the former Big Coffee space without permission.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813163000 +0000" stop="20250813170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Sweet summer science; the kids arrive at Lullah's mysterious summer camp and attempt to fix her laser; mutant mischief; the kids must face the Mutant thieves who stole their food.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813170000 +0000" stop="20250813173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny tries to keep a promise when the kids play with a strange diorama; Sara feels guilt after conning Larry out of his collectible beans.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813173000 +0000" stop="20250813180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny and the Kelp Folk try to beat Lullah at her own game; Mr. Okay worries Lullah is going to replace him.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813180000 +0000" stop="20250813183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Larry must confront his jealousy or be consumed by it; to keep a secret, Lullah is forced to help Pliny assist a grub.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813183000 +0000" stop="20250813190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>A spiraling Merian tries to figure out exactly why Francis left her party; the kids vie for a presidential sash.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813190000 +0000" stop="20250813193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>Instead of training, Robin, Jaxon and Multi set off to Lions Jungle to scout out their opponents, Team Zooganic, to see if they could gather any intel.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813193000 +0000" stop="20250813200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chibiverse</title>
    <desc>Hailey considers revealing her feelings for Scott.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813200000 +0000" stop="20250813203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Marvel's Moon Girl and Devil Dinosaur</title>
    <desc>When Lunella and Devil Dinosaur spend the weekend apart after a disagreement, Devil Dino mixes up with a rag-tag group of ex-superhero sidekicks.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813203000 +0000" stop="20250813210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Marvel's Moon Girl and Devil Dinosaur</title>
    <desc>Lunella learns that a Kree artifact is about to cause a cataclysmic storm, but when none of the adults believe her, she must swipe it herself.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813210000 +0000" stop="20250813213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Marvel's Moon Girl and Devil Dinosaur</title>
    <desc>When Pops fosters a mysterious stray dog and enters it into a dog show, a paranoid Lunella convinces the creature is an evil alien that intends to sabotage the event.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813213000 +0000" stop="20250813220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Marvel's Moon Girl and Devil Dinosaur</title>
    <desc>When Pops' rivalry with former best friend and skate partner Vernell threatens to ruin Roller Jam, Lunella meddles in their beef to squash it.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813220000 +0000" stop="20250813223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Marvel's Moon Girl and Devil Dinosaur</title>
    <desc>Lunella desperates to find a date to the school dance, but when she gets Kid Kree to be her escort, she learns that peer pressure can harm the relationships that matter most.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813223000 +0000" stop="20250813230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Marvel's Moon Girl and Devil Dinosaur</title>
    <desc>When Moon Girl teams up with the amazing super hero, Turbo, she realizes the true cost of keeping up a secret identity.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813230000 +0000" stop="20250813233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys bring Perry to the vet for a checkup and build a pet wash while they wait; Carl tries to help Perry stop Doof while working three other part-time jobs.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813233000 +0000" stop="20250814000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The Flynn-Fletchers take a cruise; Doof steals shrunken goods; Isabella struggles to lead the Fireside Girls on her own, while Doof renews his evil business license.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250814000000 +0000" stop="20250815000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys build a roller-derby rink so that their grandmother can compete against an old rival; the boys take the day off, to Candace's dismay.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-14</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
