<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv date="20250819090307 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403837/20250819.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403837&amp;date=20250819&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403837">
    <display-name lang="US">Disney XD USA - Eastern Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819000000 +0000" stop="20250819003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candance finds a lava rock necklace and Phineas and Ferb ride some waves.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819003000 +0000" stop="20250819010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace is split into two Candaces; Phineas and Ferb make a sick day triathalon.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819010000 +0000" stop="20250819013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace switches places with a princess who looks just like her; Linda and Lawrence take a trip and they entrust Candace to be in charge of the house.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819013000 +0000" stop="20250819020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>In this musical, Phineas and Ferb revisit the day they built their gigantic rollercoaster.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819020000 +0000" stop="20250819023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys invent a pair of boots that make the wearer to be faster; the kids decide to create and race a giant hot air balloon.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819023000 +0000" stop="20250819030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb build a huge biodome; Candace pays a visit to Jeremy's house.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819030000 +0000" stop="20250819033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys make a mechanical version of a historical shark; the boys take some cows to the moon.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819033000 +0000" stop="20250819040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Ferb puts together a clip show of the gang's favorite moments in celebration of Phineas' birthday.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819040000 +0000" stop="20250819043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Big Tech unveils its slate of AI-generated TV shows based on the people of Big City; Tilly's belief in positive thinking is tested when she drives Lupita's faulty go-kart.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819043000 +0000" stop="20250819050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>A hungry Cricket finds a way to speed up a restaurant's short wait; Nancy tries to stop Cricket from breaking all of Smalton's weird laws.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819050000 +0000" stop="20250819053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>The Pines family resolves to get back to normal after the Lil' Gideon incident by throwing a party.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819053000 +0000" stop="20250819060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Dipper's secret journal pages lead him and the gang to the author's hidden bunker where they find themselves face-to-face with a mysterious figure from Gravity Falls' lore.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819060000 +0000" stop="20250819063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>When Amity Blight's parents get Luz, Willow and Gus expelled from Hexside, Luz strikes a dangerous deal with them to get back into school.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819063000 +0000" stop="20250819070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>King's delusions of grandeur lead Luz, Lilith and Hooty to a perilous new island.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819070000 +0000" stop="20250819073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>CHLOROPHYLL-AINS! Francis has to protect a plant from a nefarious threat. EGGS-ISTENTIAL CRISIS! Merian struggles to open an egg salad stand with Pliny.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819073000 +0000" stop="20250819080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>LEAPIN LEGS! Merian is sent to a special place to learn how to relax. NICE TO PEAT YOU! Pliny dislodges a naturalist from a bog and joins him on a journey of discovery.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819080000 +0000" stop="20250819083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket treats his family to dinner, but Bill is suspicious about how he plans to pay for it; Tilly and Cricket battle to see if Bill lies about liking their Father's Day gifts.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819083000 +0000" stop="20250819090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Remy's plan for his whole life is thrown into question when he is unprepared for a violin recital; Gramma becomes a rideshare driver, only to find her best customers are robbers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819090000 +0000" stop="20250819093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly searches the mall for a new look to reflect her maturity; Cricket persuades Bill to buy a farming robot to get out of chores.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819093000 +0000" stop="20250819100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Chip Whistler and Bill hit it off and become friends at Farm Con; Cricket stumbles into having 100 dollars and immediately buys into a pyramid scheme.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819100000 +0000" stop="20250819103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly makes changes to her country's coming-of-age ceremony and Gramma wants none of it; Cricket fast-tracks his training for a rodeo and gets trapped in a never-ending montage.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819103000 +0000" stop="20250819110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Remy attempts to find his country grit while Cricket takes tractor-driving lessons; Phoenix journeys back to Big City to retrieve Saxon while Gramma and Gloria go to a club.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819110000 +0000" stop="20250819113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The Greens leave Big City and move back to their country farm; however, they grow unsettled when things aren't quite how they remember.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819113000 +0000" stop="20250819120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket loses his hearing and keeps it a secret from Bill; the Greens go to a hipster drive-in movie, where Gloria proves her life is fun by taking the perfect SnapAGram photo.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819120000 +0000" stop="20250819123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket wants to prove to his family that he is not dumb during trivia night at the café; Tilly gets punished for the first time and decides to break bad.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819123000 +0000" stop="20250819130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket is halted at a convenience store due to its no shoes, no service policy; when Remy throws Vasquez a surprise party, Bill's secret-keeping is put to the test.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819130000 +0000" stop="20250819133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill forces his family to embrace a live, laugh, love philosophy; Gloria tries to maintain her café's perfect rating.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819133000 +0000" stop="20250819140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>To impress her new friend, Tilly claims she saw stone gargoyles come to life; Cricket makes a deal to sell Bill's produce to a major grocery chain.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819140000 +0000" stop="20250819143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket uses his first tip from working at Big Coffee to buy a singing toy fish; Gramma kicks the family out of the house for the day, so they stay in a hotel for the first time.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819143000 +0000" stop="20250819150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma tells Cricket and Tilly that there's treasure buried on their property; Cricket adds his own doodles to Gloria's abstract paintings.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819150000 +0000" stop="20250819153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>On the trip to Big City movie multiplex, Cricket thinks he's too mature for a kids' movie, so he sneaks into a grown-up movie; Cricket registers his house on a home share website.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819153000 +0000" stop="20250819160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Cricket gets sick, his family steps in to fulfill his commitments for the day; the Green family's nemesis Chip Whistler shows up at the farmers' market in an attempt to steal business from them.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819160000 +0000" stop="20250819163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket invites the local news to see the huge watermelon Bill grew; Cricket stands up to the cyberbullying of three online gamers known as the Cyber Knights.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819163000 +0000" stop="20250819170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb care for an egg they believe belongs to Perry; the boys create their own video game starring themselves.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819170000 +0000" stop="20250819173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys accidentally knock an alien space craft while playing baseball.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819173000 +0000" stop="20250819180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry accidentally cause a townwide blackout by upsetting a Lighthouse Keeper. Kiff has dinner at the Buns's and has to hide that she hates the food.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819180000 +0000" stop="20250819183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff runs for class president against a surprise candidate, Mr. RiPeppa. The Chatterleys take Barry on their island vacation, but he seems to have a dark secret.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819183000 +0000" stop="20250819190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry try to stay awake until 4am to see a very special comet. Kiff meets a bad banana.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819190000 +0000" stop="20250819193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>Team Phalanx is hanging on to their sponsorship by a thread, with their upcoming match with Team Persona their last chance to stay in the limelight.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819193000 +0000" stop="20250819200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Midnight Mutiny; Larry wants to see what the island's nightlife has to offer; Chip mods his bod; Chip wants his rival to see him as a tough, apex predator worthy of being hunted.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819200000 +0000" stop="20250819203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater's plans are foiled by her mom's insistence that she be a "Helpful Humphrey" to the primos; Tater discovers the perfect primo-repellant in Lot Lot's creepy doll.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819203000 +0000" stop="20250819210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater is thrilled to get her very first zit; Tater shadows her cool cousin Lita as she goes about her three jobs.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819210000 +0000" stop="20250819213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater tracks down a mysterious masked skater; Tater tries to get invited to the T Sisters' gossip parties.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819213000 +0000" stop="20250819223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater tries to see into her own future; Tater teams up with the primos to get revenge on The Skid.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819223000 +0000" stop="20250819230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater helps Toñita hide a secret from Tere and Tabi; Tater tries to host a sleepover while hiding the cousins.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819230000 +0000" stop="20250819233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb herd stampeding cattle back to a carnival; the boys create a winter wonderland in the middle of summer.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250819233000 +0000" stop="20250820000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Stepbrothers keep busy during their summer vacation.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-19</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820000000 +0000" stop="20250820003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace discovers that Phineas and Ferb have invented a computer that can answer anything; Candace takes Perry to the Charity Pet Wash with her.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820003000 +0000" stop="20250820010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The phone the boys invent for Candace sends her back to Easter Island; Dr. Doofenshmirtz's new invention picks Vanessa up from class.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820010000 +0000" stop="20250820013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace gives herself a bad haircut; Doofenshmirtz enters a family meatloaf recipe with a secret ingredient into a competition.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820013000 +0000" stop="20250820020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb are cavemen and invent something useful; Dr. Doofenshmirtz tries to remodel his place; Phineas and Ferb must rescue Princess Isabella.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820020000 +0000" stop="20250820023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace spends the entire day in the backyard so that she can bust her brothers; Dr. Doofenshmirtz thinks Vanessa overhears him say he would rather have a son to do his evil bidding.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820023000 +0000" stop="20250820030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace injures her ankle and is told to stay in bed; Phineas and Ferb decide to build a truck stop diner on top of the RV.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820030000 +0000" stop="20250820033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The kids build a giant version of their favorite childhood game; Baljeet confesses that he is part of a long line of bicycle race losers.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820033000 +0000" stop="20250820040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Ferb's cousins visit from England and challenge him to a soccer match.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820040000 +0000" stop="20250820043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly tries to inspire others into community improvement by cleaning up dog droppings; Nick suggests Nancy start a U-Pick operation, but Nancy remains suspicious of his intentions.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820043000 +0000" stop="20250820050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket and Remy recall an adventure at the museum that almost derailed their friendship; Cricket learns he was unexpected.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820050000 +0000" stop="20250820053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Mabel challenges Pacifica to a miniature golf-off.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820053000 +0000" stop="20250820060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Mabel decides to put on a sock puppet rock opera to impress a local puppeteer.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820060000 +0000" stop="20250820063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>Eda gets an unwelcomed visit from a family member who puts strain on everyone in the Owl House.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820063000 +0000" stop="20250820070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>Gus tries to impress a group of cool kids from Glandus High; Luz and Amity journey into the most dangerous section of the library.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820070000 +0000" stop="20250820073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Midnight Mutiny; Larry wants to see what the island's nightlife has to offer; Chip mods his bod; Chip wants his rival to see him as a tough, apex predator worthy of being hunted.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820073000 +0000" stop="20250820080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Kids face fears to retrieve lost ball as Lullah tricks them into devious game.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820080000 +0000" stop="20250820083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Young Bill does whatever it takes to help keep the family farm in business; Tilly and Nancy enjoy Saxon's birthday at a fancy doll store.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820083000 +0000" stop="20250820090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Cricket's crush returns, Remy takes the opportunity to help Cricket get to know her; the family wants to visit a street fair, but Bill wants to stay home to save money.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820090000 +0000" stop="20250820093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When the Greens visit BigTech, Tilly discovers a chance to improve her family; Cricket wins tickets to a show and must decide who to bring.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820093000 +0000" stop="20250820100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Remy put on a play; Cricket meets his favorite heroes; when Gramma temporarily loses her eyesight, Cricket and Tilly try to help her.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820100000 +0000" stop="20250820103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Big City faces a coffee bean shortage, Cricket and Gloria's boss, Ms. Cho, challenges them to retrieve one of the few remaining sacks of coffee; when the Greens' dog, Phoenix, runs away from home, the family sets out to find her.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820103000 +0000" stop="20250820110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket and Tilly's mother, Nancy Green, returns to the city.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820110000 +0000" stop="20250820113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Bill sneaks out at night with a mysterious duffel bag, the kids hide in his truck to see where he goes; Cricket impulsively buys a giant pet snake.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820113000 +0000" stop="20250820120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill and Nancy prep a special harvest dinner; Cricket and Gramma race Tilly to get a missing ingredient; at the local community center, Tilly wants to win a trophy and begins training with the center's director.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820120000 +0000" stop="20250820123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly tries ventriloquism for the Big Coffee open mic night; the family plays the people-watching game, making up stories about city folk passing by.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820123000 +0000" stop="20250820130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The Greens go on a family visit to the dentist's office, where Cricket is determined to avoid Dr. Enamel and power through his toothache.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820130000 +0000" stop="20250820133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Nancy's trailer is stolen by her old biker gang, the kids resolve to get it back; Cricket house-sits for Remy, but things go awry when the rest of the Greens visit.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820133000 +0000" stop="20250820140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>At the Valentine's Dance, Cricket develops an unwanted crush on Gabriella; Cricket joins forces with Officer Keys to hunt down a neighborhood litterbug.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820140000 +0000" stop="20250820143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma spurns Tilly at the city park, so Tilly tries making her jealous; Gramma makes special biscuits for the kids when they're hurt, but won't make more when they're better.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820143000 +0000" stop="20250820150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket stages a crisis by letting skunks into the cafe, but it gets out of control; Nancy accidentally destroys Saxon, but Tilly mistakenly directs her wrath at Gramma.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820150000 +0000" stop="20250820153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Remy and Cricket get their own apartment, they discover that nonstop fun leads to chaos; Tilly volunteers at the animal shelter but doesn't want to part with any of the animals.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820153000 +0000" stop="20250820160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly takes Gramma out to be a tourist for a day; Cricket and Remy arrange a dinner party for everyone to get to know each other.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820160000 +0000" stop="20250820163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>To impress her new friend, Tilly claims she saw stone gargoyles come to life; Cricket makes a deal to sell Bill's produce to a major grocery chain.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820163000 +0000" stop="20250820170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Major Monogram and Dr. Doofenshmirtz host a countdown of the top 10 musical numbers from the series.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820170000 +0000" stop="20250820173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>While in the future to obtain a new tool, Phineas and Ferb run into future Candace.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820173000 +0000" stop="20250820180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>The Chatterleys get ready; Kiff and the crew run the morning announcements at school and it gets out of control.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820180000 +0000" stop="20250820183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and the crew learn magic, but end up in over their heads; Helen casts a spell on Kiff and Barry and won't tell them what it is.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820183000 +0000" stop="20250820190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry pick up trash in the park but can't decide what is trash; Trevor works out his frustrations by writing libelous stories about Kiff and Barry.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820190000 +0000" stop="20250820193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>After failing Warden's Exam, Robin wonders if he can ever get to the same level as his teammates.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820193000 +0000" stop="20250820200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>LEAPIN LEGS! Merian is sent to a special place to learn how to relax. NICE TO PEAT YOU! Pliny dislodges a naturalist from a bog and joins him on a journey of discovery.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820200000 +0000" stop="20250820203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff's plan to infiltrate a group sleepover and learn its secrets all depends on Barry's ability to lie; Kiff and Barry try to get nicknamed by a local movie theater ticket taker.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820203000 +0000" stop="20250820210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Table Town School puts on its first musical, but it's all about Helen; the Chatterleys encounter obstacles during their weekly grocery shopping trip.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820210000 +0000" stop="20250820213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff attempts to help Candle and Trevor with their new friendship; Miss Deer Teacher goes to Kiff for dating advice, not knowing Kiff has been getting her tips from a soap opera.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820213000 +0000" stop="20250820220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff leads a group to the mall to get a free pretzel, but leadership comes with responsibilities; Kiff and Barry try to learn more about the mysterious Ghost Wolf.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820220000 +0000" stop="20250820223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>A new collection craze wraps up the crew, resulting in rising tensions; when Kiff shadows Harry and Terri as they watch Kristophe, she learns that being in charge is not so easy.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820223000 +0000" stop="20250820230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry help a local bridge troll but discover he has some tricky riddles; Kiff and Barry get detention and meet a ragtag team of students who help them plot an escape.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820230000 +0000" stop="20250820233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas enters a thumb-wrestling contest with Buford; Candace tries out for the lead in her favorite play.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250820233000 +0000" stop="20250821000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Stepbrothers keep busy during their summer vacation.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-20</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250821000000 +0000" stop="20250822000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Perry wins a contest and becomes the spokesanimal for Totally Tools.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-21</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
