<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv date="20250811091114 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403837/20250811.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403837&amp;date=20250811&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403837">
    <display-name lang="US">Disney XD USA - Eastern Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811000000 +0000" stop="20250811003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys create a Perry that can go anywhere and do everything with them; Candace's plans to watch over the boys backfire.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811003000 +0000" stop="20250811010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Meap returns to save Phineas and Ferb from his nemesis Mitch; Dr. Doofenshmirtz decides to revisit his former nemesis, Peter the Panda.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811010000 +0000" stop="20250811013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace asks the boys to invent a device; the boys invent a brain booster.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811013000 +0000" stop="20250811020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Mothership produces a reality show starring all of A-Spen's friends; Eliza gets involved in a feud between werewolves and sasquatches.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811020000 +0000" stop="20250811023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>A digital phantom of his younger self haunts Zedy; Addison must find a way to silence her inner critic before she gives up on art altogether.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811023000 +0000" stop="20250811030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Bucky experiences what it's like to be a werewolf; determined to win Seabrook's quiz bowl, Eliza builds a W-band to help her partner Wynter to focus.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811030000 +0000" stop="20250811033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket and Remy recall an adventure at the museum that almost derailed their friendship; Cricket learns he was unexpected.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811033000 +0000" stop="20250811040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The mischievous Cricket Green and his family pick up their lives in the country to start anew in the big city.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811040000 +0000" stop="20250811043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Sweet summer science; the kids arrive at Lullah's mysterious summer camp and attempt to fix her laser; mutant mischief; the kids must face the Mutant thieves who stole their food.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811043000 +0000" stop="20250811050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny tries to keep a promise when the kids play with a strange diorama; Sara feels guilt after conning Larry out of his collectible beans.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811050000 +0000" stop="20250811053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Lullah wants alone time and creates a Manatee-Nanny to watch the kids; Pliny must choose - support Larry's noodling habit or keep him safe.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811053000 +0000" stop="20250811060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip wants to make a breakfast that will blow his friends' socks off; Larry saves a baby lizard and swears to protect it from harm.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811060000 +0000" stop="20250811063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater's "Summer of Tater" agenda veers unexpectedly as her twelve primos surprisingly move in; perplexed by BiBi's dramatic scheme, Tater tries to get the primos to sign a room contract.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811063000 +0000" stop="20250811070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater's plans are foiled by her mom's insistence that she be a "Helpful Humphrey" to the primos; Tater discovers the perfect primo-repellant in Lot Lot's creepy doll.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811070000 +0000" stop="20250811073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater is inspired by a "10-Under-10" list of impressive kids; Tater regrets giving her "baby" books to the younger primos.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811073000 +0000" stop="20250811080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater is thrilled to get her very first zit; Tater shadows her cool cousin Lita as she goes about her three jobs.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811080000 +0000" stop="20250811083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>A hungry Cricket finds a way to speed up a restaurant's short wait; Nancy tries to stop Cricket from breaking all of Smalton's weird laws.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811083000 +0000" stop="20250811090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Big Tech unveils its slate of AI-generated TV shows based on the people of Big City; Tilly's belief in positive thinking is tested when she drives Lupita's faulty go-kart.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811090000 +0000" stop="20250811093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The Greens get the work out of their life at Big Citys new gym; cricket finds a loophole to his curfew that will let him attend a late-night drone show.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811093000 +0000" stop="20250811100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma assembles a seaworthy crew to retrieve packages stolen by Big City's porch pirates; Nick creates a fake scouting troop to trick Cricket and Tilly into raising money for him.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811100000 +0000" stop="20250811103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The Greens leave Big City and move back to their country farm; however, they grow unsettled when things aren't quite how they remember.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811103000 +0000" stop="20250811110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>While Cricket shows Remy the fun of country life, Tilly seeks new sleeping arrangements; Cricket tries to win back his old country friend, Hector.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811110000 +0000" stop="20250811113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Remy attempts to find his country grit while Cricket takes tractor-driving lessons; Phoenix journeys back to Big City to retrieve Saxon while Gramma and Gloria go to a club.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811113000 +0000" stop="20250811120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Brooke Dillman guest stars as diner owner Patti; Nancy tries to get Cricket to cut his new rat tail without admitting that she hates it.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811120000 +0000" stop="20250811123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly makes changes to her country's coming-of-age ceremony and Gramma wants none of it; Cricket fast-tracks his training for a rodeo and gets trapped in a never-ending montage.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811123000 +0000" stop="20250811130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>A pizza delivery girl from Big City has to flee from a crazed country family; when Bill gets a horse for the day, Tilly must hide how much she secretly hates horses.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811130000 +0000" stop="20250811133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Andromeda exchange letters that reveal their outlooks on the world; Remy enlists the Greens to help him lie to his parents about his week in the country.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811133000 +0000" stop="20250811140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The kids plan a heist to steal honey from Bill's beehive; Cricket and Remy run a campaign to get Phoenix, the dog, elected as mayor.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811140000 +0000" stop="20250811143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket discovers lake life brings out Bill's fun-loving side; when rabbits threaten to destroy Bill's crops, Nancy enlists their country friends to save the harvest.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811143000 +0000" stop="20250811150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When the Greens return Gramma and Remy to Big City, they are determined to delay their goodbyes for as long as possible.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811150000 +0000" stop="20250811153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Cricket wrestle with decision making at a truck stop between Big City and the country; Tilly rises through the ranks as a Big City jingle writer.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811153000 +0000" stop="20250811160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill discovers his favorite comedian, Fred the Farmer, may not be who he claims to be; Tilly defends Cricket at a family trial after he's accused of stealing an entire cake.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811160000 +0000" stop="20250811163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket and Tilly get to know their grandpa; Nancy scrambles to find him a job; to ensure his family's future security, Bill becomes a hoarder.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811163000 +0000" stop="20250811170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Merian tries to save Dr. Lullah's fish counter from a life of busy work; the kids put on a play to warn mutants about a disaster.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811170000 +0000" stop="20250811173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Kids face fears to retrieve lost ball as Lullah tricks them into devious game.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811173000 +0000" stop="20250811180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Midnight Mutiny; Larry wants to see what the island's nightlife has to offer; Chip mods his bod; Chip wants his rival to see him as a tough, apex predator worthy of being hunted.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811180000 +0000" stop="20250811183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>LEAPIN LEGS! Merian is sent to a special place to learn how to relax. NICE TO PEAT YOU! Pliny dislodges a naturalist from a bog and joins him on a journey of discovery.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811183000 +0000" stop="20250811190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>CHLOROPHYLL-AINS! Francis has to protect a plant from a nefarious threat. EGGS-ISTENTIAL CRISIS! Merian struggles to open an egg salad stand with Pliny.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811190000 +0000" stop="20250811193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>Now that they're officially pros, the hunt is on for Team Persona's Bey Sponsor, who will help them train and climb The X.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811193000 +0000" stop="20250811200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chibiverse</title>
    <desc>Penny and Molly are excited to present an adorable chibi pet parade, until a group of sinister Chibi villains, led by King Andrias, arrives to take over the Chibiverse.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811200000 +0000" stop="20250811203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Zed, Addison and the Seabrook crew get to redo their senior year together; Zed creates a new drink called zoda that transforms the entire school into zoda-obsessed zombies.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811203000 +0000" stop="20250811210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Eliza and Bucky compete to see whose vending machine is better; Zed and Addison use their free period to help the stressed-out A-spen learn to let loose.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811210000 +0000" stop="20250811213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Wynter and A-spen start a band, but they may not reconcile their differing musical visions; Willa and Bucky put Wyatt through an alpha-dog-bootcamp to help him win over Eliza.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811213000 +0000" stop="20250811220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Bucky turns the school into a Bucky-themed dystopia; when Bonzo discovers mysterious blueprints in the diner, he becomes possessed by the desire to build a Spaghetti Waterfall.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811220000 +0000" stop="20250811223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Addison is determined to help Dae, the quirky new witch at school, feel welcome; Zed and little sister Zoey must team up to fight a monster hunter.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811223000 +0000" stop="20250811230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Zombies: The Re-Animated Series</title>
    <desc>Zed and his friends find a mini fridge, but it is too mini for them to share; Bree wants to get into the Cheer Hall(way) of Fame, but a negative comment destroys her confidence.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811230000 +0000" stop="20250811233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys decide to ramp up their local summer block party with supersized attractions; the kids work to save Mom after she is hit by Doof's inator.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250811233000 +0000" stop="20250812000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The kids build a giant submarine sandwich submarine while Doof steals food; Candace tries to bust the boys while taking her driving test; Doof causes chaos in traffic.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-11</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812000000 +0000" stop="20250812003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys build the world's greatest roller coaster; Candace is surprised during a trip to Mount Rushmore.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812003000 +0000" stop="20250812010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys enter the family automobile in a car race; then, a tropical beach paradise in the backyard goes awry.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812010000 +0000" stop="20250812013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb herd stampeding cattle back to a carnival; the boys create a winter wonderland in the middle of summer.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812013000 +0000" stop="20250812020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys capture Candace, who is wrapped up like a mummy; Phineas and the Ferb-Tones become a one-hit wonder.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812020000 +0000" stop="20250812023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas enters a thumb-wrestling contest with Buford; Candace tries out for the lead in her favorite play.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812023000 +0000" stop="20250812030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys scare Candace with a fake Bigfoot; Phineas and Ferb create treehouses for themselves and Candace.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812030000 +0000" stop="20250812033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Dr. Doofenshmirtz makes Perry the Platypus jealous with his new nemesis; Phineas and Ferb travel back in time.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812033000 +0000" stop="20250812040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb create a circus for the neighborhood; the boys market a wooden toy version of Perry the platypus.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812040000 +0000" stop="20250812043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket gets dumped by his girlfriend, so he tries to change to win her back; Bill becomes hyper-competitive when Cricket starts to be better at things than him.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812043000 +0000" stop="20250812050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The mischievous Cricket Green and his family pick up their lives in the country to start anew in the big city.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812050000 +0000" stop="20250812053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Dipper is self-conscious that Mabel is taller than him so he seeks out a magic way to grow himself.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812053000 +0000" stop="20250812060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Dipper and Mabel are excited to join in on the fun, but when Wendy casually mentions that trick-or-treating is for kids, Dipper's whole outlook on the evening changes.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812060000 +0000" stop="20250812063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>King finally becomes a successful author by writing a bestseller; his books fly off the shelves, but then he finds out that he should have read the small print.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812063000 +0000" stop="20250812070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>Luz needs to learn a new spell, so Eda trains her in a magical place on the island.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812070000 +0000" stop="20250812073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Sweet summer science; the kids arrive at Lullah's mysterious summer camp and attempt to fix her laser; mutant mischief; the kids must face the Mutant thieves who stole their food.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812073000 +0000" stop="20250812080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny tries to keep a promise when the kids play with a strange diorama; Sara feels guilt after conning Larry out of his collectible beans.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812080000 +0000" stop="20250812083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>To impress her new friend, Tilly claims she saw stone gargoyles come to life; Cricket makes a deal to sell Bill's produce to a major grocery chain.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812083000 +0000" stop="20250812090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket uses his first tip from working at Big Coffee to buy a singing toy fish; Gramma kicks the family out of the house for the day, so they stay in a hotel for the first time.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812090000 +0000" stop="20250812093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma tells Cricket and Tilly that there's treasure buried on their property; Cricket adds his own doodles to Gloria's abstract paintings.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812093000 +0000" stop="20250812100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>On the trip to Big City movie multiplex, Cricket thinks he's too mature for a kids' movie, so he sneaks into a grown-up movie; Cricket registers his house on a home share website.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812100000 +0000" stop="20250812103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>After being mocked for his handshake, Cricket trains for a Western-style handshake duel; Gloria combines her work life and social life by hiring her friends as employees.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812103000 +0000" stop="20250812110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma butts heads with Nick when he crashes her special family hockey outing; Chip Whistler recounts what happened to him since "Chipocalypse Now.".</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812110000 +0000" stop="20250812113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly goes down an internet rabbit hole to figure out what happened to her favorite ice cream treat; Cricket tries to teach Gregly how to make friends.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812113000 +0000" stop="20250812120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill just wants Tilly to come down from a tree; when Remy tells Vasquez that he no longer needs his protection, Vasquez speaks with a therapist.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812120000 +0000" stop="20250812123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>A nature documentary portrays Big City as a wild ecosystem; avid collector Remy struggles to cope after Cricket finds the rarest of all trading cards.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812123000 +0000" stop="20250812130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>To prove to his parents that he is money-wise, Remy starts his own business; feeling neglected by his family, Bill befriends a murder of crows.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812130000 +0000" stop="20250812133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket tries to avoid a fortune teller's ominous prediction that he will get a stinky slap; in an inescapable escape room, Cricket must decide between family and freedom.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812133000 +0000" stop="20250812140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket is caught eating dog food by Gloria and must stop her from revealing his secret shame; Bill installs a parenting device to monitor and discipline Cricket for him.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812140000 +0000" stop="20250812143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill receives a surprise; Jade's boss suspends her from work.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812143000 +0000" stop="20250812150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket tries to come up with the perfect prank to play on his girlfriend on April Fool's Day; Bill goes to extremes to prevent Tilly from experiencing grief.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812150000 +0000" stop="20250812153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Chip Whistler attempts to create an evil family, so he takes down the Greens; the Greens move to the suburbs and live under new identities to hide from Chip.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812153000 +0000" stop="20250812160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The Greens cause trouble during free sample day at the Farmers Market; Cricket and Nancy toilet paper all of Smalton in a quest for pranking glory.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812160000 +0000" stop="20250812163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>In summer, Cricket impulsively eats Bill's chocolate Santa and must replace it; when Gramma's serene country retreat is disrupted by an outdoor festival, she resolves to stop it.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812163000 +0000" stop="20250812170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>The kids get sucked into a white-hot, Mutant soap opera; Sara attempts to nail the perfect hairstyle so she can be the star of Francis' painting.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812170000 +0000" stop="20250812173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Merian takes on the case of a destructive space chimp; Pliny wants to play Geoplomacy when the kids discover six sandbars.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812173000 +0000" stop="20250812180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip becomes a spy to prove he's not a nincompoop; after a close call, daredevil Larry embraces a life of extreme caution.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812180000 +0000" stop="20250812183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Sara lies in order to join the kids' Elephant Triumvirate book club; Larry asks Mr. Okay to help unlock the true power of his dud Zorb.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812183000 +0000" stop="20250812190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>A Mutant trio sets out to discover the purpose of some weird-shaped berries; a new visitor offers the kids the summer of their dreams.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812190000 +0000" stop="20250812193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>Now that Team Persona is officially sponsored by Komaba Sushi, the team is finally ready to battle at The X.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812193000 +0000" stop="20250812200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Chibiverse</title>
    <desc>Everyone's favorite squirrel, Kiff, hosts a game show.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812200000 +0000" stop="20250812203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry try to stay awake until 4am to see a very special comet. Kiff meets a bad banana.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812203000 +0000" stop="20250812210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>The Chatterleys get ready; Kiff and the crew run the morning announcements at school and it gets out of control.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812210000 +0000" stop="20250812213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and the crew learn magic, but end up in over their heads; Helen casts a spell on Kiff and Barry and won't tell them what it is.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812213000 +0000" stop="20250812220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry pick up trash in the park but can't decide what is trash; Trevor works out his frustrations by writing libelous stories about Kiff and Barry.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812220000 +0000" stop="20250812223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff's good deed goes unnoticed while Reggie's receives lots of attention; Kiff and Barry enjoy a kids-only dinner with their shy classmate Darryn.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812223000 +0000" stop="20250812230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff's thirst for life takes her on countless adventures through their city alongside her best friend, Barry.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812230000 +0000" stop="20250812233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys build an endless ice luge to beat the heat while Doof brings oil to a waterpark; Candace and Doof see the same psychologist, who thinks their experiences may be connected.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250812233000 +0000" stop="20250813000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys build a zoetrope that goes on an adventure of its own; the kids build a bookcase that gets attacked by an army of Doof-plants.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-12</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250813000000 +0000" stop="20250814000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace joins a jousting tournament at the Renaissance festival; the boys build robot clones of themselves to complete more projects.</desc>
    <date>2025-08-13</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
