<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv date="20250729091722 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403837/20250729.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403837&amp;date=20250729&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403837">
    <display-name lang="US">Disney XD USA - Eastern Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729000000 +0000" stop="20250729002500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Win or Lose</title>
    <desc>Kai moves to a new town with her father, seeking a fresh start and joining the local softball team; a good player, she makes friends while facing pressure from her father to improve.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729002500 +0000" stop="20250729010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Win or Lose</title>
    <desc>Dan takes his role as coach seriously and strives to teach the Pickles life lessons while respecting the game; he knows his authority is important as his team works to win the championship.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729010000 +0000" stop="20250729013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Vanessa and Doof travel to Drusselstein while the boys dig for Mom's lost wedding ring; The kids build a bird mansion for a rare macaw while Doof deals with giant praying mantises.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729013000 +0000" stop="20250729020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>While Cricket shows Remy the fun of country life, Tilly seeks new sleeping arrangements; Cricket tries to win back his old country friend, Hector.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729020000 +0000" stop="20250729023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Remy attempts to find his country grit while Cricket takes tractor-driving lessons; Phoenix journeys back to Big City to retrieve Saxon while Gramma and Gloria go to a club.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729023000 +0000" stop="20250729030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Brooke Dillman guest stars as diner owner Patti; Nancy tries to get Cricket to cut his new rat tail without admitting that she hates it.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729030000 +0000" stop="20250729033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket gets dumped by his girlfriend, so he tries to change to win her back; Bill becomes hyper-competitive when Cricket starts to be better at things than him.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729033000 +0000" stop="20250729040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Chip enacts his ultimate revenge plan by framing the Green family for ruining Big City and turning everyone against them.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729040000 +0000" stop="20250729043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Identity crises abound; Wayne wants city excitement.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729043000 +0000" stop="20250729050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma assembles a seaworthy crew to retrieve packages stolen by Big City's porch pirates; Nick creates a fake scouting troop to trick Cricket and Tilly into raising money for him.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729050000 +0000" stop="20250729053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Pacifica enlists Dipper's help to rid the Northwest Mansion of a ghost.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729053000 +0000" stop="20250729060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>After government agents take Stan into custody, Dipper and Mabel question how much they really know about their Grunkle Stan.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729060000 +0000" stop="20250729063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>Luz is desperate for more information about Philip Wittebane, the creator of the portal door; with Lilith's help, she sets off on a journey for the ages.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729063000 +0000" stop="20250729070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>Hunter goes under cover at Hexside for his most important mission yet; Willow determines to succeed at an exciting new sport.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729070000 +0000" stop="20250729073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Larry seeks to explore the island's nighttime entertainment; Chip aims to impress his rival by presenting himself as a formidable, apex predator worth hunting.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729073000 +0000" stop="20250729080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>CHLOROPHYLL-AINS! Francis has to protect a plant from a nefarious threat. EGGS-ISTENTIAL CRISIS! Merian struggles to open an egg salad stand with Pliny.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729080000 +0000" stop="20250729083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Remy and Cricket get their own apartment, they discover that nonstop fun leads to chaos; Tilly volunteers at the animal shelter but doesn't want to part with any of the animals.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729083000 +0000" stop="20250729090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket stages a crisis by letting skunks into the cafe, but it gets out of control; Nancy accidentally destroys Saxon, but Tilly mistakenly directs her wrath at Gramma.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729090000 +0000" stop="20250729093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma spurns Tilly at the city park, so Tilly tries making her jealous; Gramma makes special biscuits for the kids when they're hurt, but won't make more when they're better.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729093000 +0000" stop="20250729100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>At the Valentine's Dance, Cricket develops an unwanted crush on Gabriella; Cricket joins forces with Officer Keys to hunt down a neighborhood litterbug.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729100000 +0000" stop="20250729103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Young Bill does whatever it takes to help keep the family farm in business; Tilly and Nancy enjoy Saxon's birthday at a fancy doll store.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729103000 +0000" stop="20250729110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Cricket's crush returns, Remy takes the opportunity to help Cricket get to know her; the family wants to visit a street fair, but Bill wants to stay home to save money.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729110000 +0000" stop="20250729113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When the Greens visit BigTech, Tilly discovers a chance to improve her family; Cricket wins tickets to a show and must decide who to bring.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729113000 +0000" stop="20250729120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Remy put on a play; Cricket meets his favorite heroes; when Gramma temporarily loses her eyesight, Cricket and Tilly try to help her.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729120000 +0000" stop="20250729123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket struggles to get the best birthday present for his best bud, Remy; due to a close call with a dirt bike, Cricket fearfully decides to live his life in shelter.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729123000 +0000" stop="20250729130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>At the library, the Greens try to find a book, but a scary librarian threatens them into being quiet; Chip decides if he is really the failure Cricket says he is.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729130000 +0000" stop="20250729133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Chip Whistler tears down the buildings around the Green's house to build a Wholesome Foods store.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729133000 +0000" stop="20250729140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Gloria's parents visit, she ropes the Greens into escalating lies about her success; Cricket goes on a quest to find the best pool in Big City.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729140000 +0000" stop="20250729143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>On New Year's Eve, Cricket insists on helping Gloria complete her resolution of approaching her crush, Kevin; Cricket and Remy challenge Vasquez to a snowball fight; Tilly creates a snowperson.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729143000 +0000" stop="20250729150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When the kids play a role-playing game at Remy's, his rules lead to conflict; when the Greens go out for karaoke, Tilly struggles to decide what genre of music will best express her true self.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729150000 +0000" stop="20250729153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill chaperones Cricket and Gabriella's first date; a disagreement between Cricket and Tilly turns into reality-TV-like entertainment for Gloria and Gramma.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729153000 +0000" stop="20250729160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket teaches the local kids a new curse word, threatening to ruin the community center's choir performance; the Greens try new methods to improve sales at their produce stand.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729160000 +0000" stop="20250729163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket tries to prove to Bill he can eat fast food for every meal; Tilly and Cricket debate whether the lives of people in Big City are connected.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729163000 +0000" stop="20250729170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Doof becomes a mothman; the boys make a movie set.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729170000 +0000" stop="20250729173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Meap enlists Candace and the kids to help bust his nemesis, Mitch, before he can steal a long-lost treasure hidden somewhere on Earth.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729173000 +0000" stop="20250729180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Phineas and Ferb spin the house in order to paint it more quickly.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729180000 +0000" stop="20250729183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>When the boys are mistaken as a super hero, a villain arrives in town to challenge them.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729183000 +0000" stop="20250729190000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>When Irving's brother, Albert, calls Phineas and Ferb fakes, Buford and Baljeet pretend to be the boys so that Irving can prove Albert wrong; Candace runs a bust camp in her backyard to prep for busting Phineas and Ferb.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729190000 +0000" stop="20250729193000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Beyblade X</title>
    <desc>Right before their match at the top of The X, Robin heads back to his hometown with Jaxon.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729193000 +0000" stop="20250729200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Merian takes on the case of a destructive space chimp; Pliny wants to play Geoplomacy when the kids discover six sandbars.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729200000 +0000" stop="20250729203000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and friends invent a game that becomes a professional sport; Kiff and Secretary Prince break Principal Secretary's juice machine and must find him a new one.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729203000 +0000" stop="20250729210000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Trevor becomes the foundation of the newest Table Town School craze, but at what cost? Kiff, Barry and Terri go to the Table Town Mall, but get caught up in a long line.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729210000 +0000" stop="20250729213000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry accompany Trollie on a mission to his magical neighborhood; the Chatterley family heads to Okaywill for new winter coats.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729213000 +0000" stop="20250729220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>A trip to the aquarium! Kiff worries that she's annoying.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729220000 +0000" stop="20250729223000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and Barry go on an adventure outside of Table Town to save Halfway There Day!</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729223000 +0000" stop="20250729230000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff's thirst for life takes her on countless adventures through their city alongside her best friend, Barry.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729230000 +0000" stop="20250729233000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff's thirst for life takes her on countless adventures through their city alongside her best friend, Barry.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250729233000 +0000" stop="20250730000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff's thirst for life takes her on countless adventures through their city alongside her best friend, Barry.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730000000 +0000" stop="20250730003000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>A spiraling Merian tries to figure out exactly why Francis left her party; the kids vie for a presidential sash.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730003000 +0000" stop="20250730010000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Primos</title>
    <desc>Tater and the primos help Buela fulfill her American dream.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730010000 +0000" stop="20250730013000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Trevor becomes the foundation of the newest Table Town School craze, but at what cost? Kiff, Barry and Terri go to the Table Town Mall, but get caught up in a long line.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730013000 +0000" stop="20250730020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Kiff</title>
    <desc>Kiff and friends invent a game that becomes a professional sport; Kiff and Secretary Prince break Principal Secretary's juice machine and must find him a new one.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730020000 +0000" stop="20250730023000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The kids build a giant submarine sandwich submarine while Doof steals food; Candace tries to bust the boys while taking her driving test; Doof causes chaos in traffic.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730023000 +0000" stop="20250730030000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys build an endless ice luge to beat the heat while Doof brings oil to a waterpark; Candace and Doof see the same psychologist, who thinks their experiences may be connected.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730030000 +0000" stop="20250730033000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Big Tech unveils its slate of AI-generated TV shows based on the people of Big City; Tilly's belief in positive thinking is tested when she drives Lupita's faulty go-kart.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730033000 +0000" stop="20250730040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>A hungry Cricket finds a way to speed up a restaurant's short wait; Nancy tries to stop Cricket from breaking all of Smalton's weird laws.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730040000 +0000" stop="20250730043000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Cricket wrestle with decision making at a truck stop between Big City and the country; Tilly rises through the ranks as a Big City jingle writer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730043000 +0000" stop="20250730050000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill discovers his favorite comedian, Fred the Farmer, may not be who he claims to be; Tilly defends Cricket at a family trial after he's accused of stealing an entire cake.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730050000 +0000" stop="20250730053000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Cornered underneath the Mystery Shack, Stan must finally reveal the secrets of his past and his mysterious portal to Dipper and Mabel.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730053000 +0000" stop="20250730060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gravity Falls</title>
    <desc>Dipper finds an unlikely friend to join him with his newest obsession, a board game called Dungeons, Dungeons &amp; More Dungeons.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730060000 +0000" stop="20250730063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>Amity wants to prove herself to her father; Luz thinks she's found the perfect way to do it: underground witch duels.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730063000 +0000" stop="20250730070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Owl House</title>
    <desc>Eda tells a story from her teen years: the day she met Raine Whispers.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730070000 +0000" stop="20250730073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Merian takes on the case of a destructive space chimp; Pliny wants to play Geoplomacy when the kids discover six sandbars.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730073000 +0000" stop="20250730080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>A Mutant trio sets out to discover the purpose of some weird-shaped berries; a new visitor offers the kids the summer of their dreams.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730080000 +0000" stop="20250730083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>When Nancy's trailer is stolen by her old biker gang, the kids resolve to get it back; Cricket house-sits for Remy, but things go awry when the rest of the Greens visit.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730083000 +0000" stop="20250730090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>The Greens go on a family visit to the dentist's office, where Cricket is determined to avoid Dr. Enamel and power through his toothache.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730090000 +0000" stop="20250730093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly tries ventriloquism for the Big Coffee open mic night; the family plays the people-watching game, making up stories about city folk passing by.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730093000 +0000" stop="20250730100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill and Nancy prep a special harvest dinner; Cricket and Gramma race Tilly to get a missing ingredient; at the local community center, Tilly wants to win a trophy and begins training with the center's director.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730100000 +0000" stop="20250730103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Remy uses Cricket's antics to gain views and likes on a new video-sharing app; Gloria gives Tilly and Cricket a tour of the animation studio where she's interning.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730103000 +0000" stop="20250730110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma and Cricket fume over an unsightly van parked in front of their house; Nancy joins Cricket and Tilly's Little League team to get back at their unsportsmanlike rivals.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730110000 +0000" stop="20250730113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly revives Cousin Jilly, an alter-ego she created to entertain Cricket when they were younger; Gloria opens a secret café in the former Big Coffee space without permission.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730113000 +0000" stop="20250730120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly and Cricket wrestle with decision making at a truck stop between Big City and the country; Tilly rises through the ranks as a Big City jingle writer.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730120000 +0000" stop="20250730123000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill discovers his favorite comedian, Fred the Farmer, may not be who he claims to be; Tilly defends Cricket at a family trial after he's accused of stealing an entire cake.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730123000 +0000" stop="20250730130000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket and Tilly get to know their grandpa; Nancy scrambles to find him a job; to ensure his family's future security, Bill becomes a hoarder.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730130000 +0000" stop="20250730133000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>After being mocked for his handshake, Cricket trains for a Western-style handshake duel; Gloria combines her work life and social life by hiring her friends as employees.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730133000 +0000" stop="20250730140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Gramma butts heads with Nick when he crashes her special family hockey outing; Chip Whistler recounts what happened to him since "Chipocalypse Now.".</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730140000 +0000" stop="20250730143000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Tilly goes down an internet rabbit hole to figure out what happened to her favorite ice cream treat; Cricket tries to teach Gregly how to make friends.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730143000 +0000" stop="20250730150000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Bill just wants Tilly to come down from a tree; when Remy tells Vasquez that he no longer needs his protection, Vasquez speaks with a therapist.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730150000 +0000" stop="20250730153000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>A nature documentary portrays Big City as a wild ecosystem; avid collector Remy struggles to cope after Cricket finds the rarest of all trading cards.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730153000 +0000" stop="20250730160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>To prove to his parents that he is money-wise, Remy starts his own business; feeling neglected by his family, Bill befriends a murder of crows.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730160000 +0000" stop="20250730163000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens</title>
    <desc>Cricket tries to avoid a fortune teller's ominous prediction that he will get a stinky slap; in an inescapable escape room, Cricket must decide between family and freedom.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730163000 +0000" stop="20250730170000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The kids have a sleepover; Doof's cousin traps Perry.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730170000 +0000" stop="20250730173000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Buford's Candace suit comes to life and tries to take over the real Candace's life; Candace ignores her brothers for a day in order to help her Mom with a bust of her own.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730173000 +0000" stop="20250730180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>The boys' chameleon grows to a dinosaur's size; Phineas and Ferb put on a rodeo with robotic bulls.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730180000 +0000" stop="20250730183000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Building an ATV; Creating the world's tallest building.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730183000 +0000" stop="20250730190500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Phineas and Ferb</title>
    <desc>Candace becomes mayor for the day; ultimate lemonade stand.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730190500 +0000" stop="20250730193500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny tries to keep a promise when the kids play with a strange diorama; Sara feels guilt after conning Larry out of his collectible beans.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730193500 +0000" stop="20250730201000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Sweet summer science; the kids arrive at Lullah's mysterious summer camp and attempt to fix her laser; mutant mischief; the kids must face the Mutant thieves who stole their food.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730201000 +0000" stop="20250730204500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Pliny and the Kelp Folk try to beat Lullah at her own game; Mr. Okay worries Lullah is going to replace him.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730204500 +0000" stop="20250730211500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Merian tries to save Dr. Lullah's fish counter from a life of busy work; the kids put on a play to warn mutants about a disaster.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730211500 +0000" stop="20250730215000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Larry seeks to explore the island's nighttime entertainment; Chip aims to impress his rival by presenting himself as a formidable, apex predator worth hunting.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730215000 +0000" stop="20250730222000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>The kids get sucked into a white-hot, Mutant soap opera; Sara attempts to nail the perfect hairstyle so she can be the star of Francis' painting.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730222000 +0000" stop="20250730225500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Chip becomes a spy to prove he's not a nincompoop; after a close call, daredevil Larry embraces a life of extreme caution.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730225500 +0000" stop="20250730232500 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>Sara lies in order to join the kids' Elephant Triumvirate book club; Larry asks Mr. Okay to help unlock the true power of his dud Zorb.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250730232500 +0000" stop="20250731000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">StuGo</title>
    <desc>A Mutant trio sets out to discover the purpose of some weird-shaped berries; a new visitor offers the kids the summer of their dreams.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403837" start="20250731000000 +0000" stop="20250801000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Big City Greens the Movie: Spacecation</title>
    <desc>Thrill-seeker Cricket Green tricks his country family into taking a road trip in space, which ends up endangering all of Big City.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-31</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
