<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> <!DOCTYPE tv SYSTEM "xmltv.dtd">
<tv date="20250629101912 +0800" generator-info-name="epg.pw" generator-info-url="https://epg.pw/channels/403490/20250629.html" source-info-name="FREE EPG" source-info-url="https://epg.pw/api/epg.xml?channel_id=403490&amp;date=20250629&amp;timezone=None">
  <channel id="403490">
    <display-name lang="US">Hallmark - Eastern Feed</display-name>
    <icon src="" />
  </channel>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250629000000 +0000" stop="20250629020100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Machu Picchu Proposal</title>
    <desc>Katie helps plan her brother's proposal atop Machu Picchu. When the proposal is ruined by spontaneous Chef Carlos, Katie enlists Carlos to help her find the most romantic spot in all of Peru. Stars Rhiannon Fish and Alec Santos.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250629020100 +0000" stop="20250629040100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">To Barcelona, Forever</title>
    <desc>As Anna travels back to Barcelona, reuniting with Erica to celebrate her engagement to Nico, she meets a charming farmer and accidentally finds herself engaged to save his family's legacy.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250629040100 +0000" stop="20250629060100 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Cross Country Christmas</title>
    <desc>When a snowstorm disrupts both Lina's and Max's holiday plans, they realize they must work together to find a way home -- without taking it out on each other.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250629060100 +0000" stop="20250629080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Christmas Melody</title>
    <desc>A single mother moves back to her hometown with her young daughter. Having a hard time adjusting, the daughter seeks help from her music teacher to write a song for the Christmas variety show.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250629080000 +0000" stop="20250629100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christmas Waltz</title>
    <desc>A woman makes an unexpected connection with her dance instructor after her storybook Christmas wedding is canceled.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250629100000 +0000" stop="20250629120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Heavenly Christmas</title>
    <desc>A workaholic's (Kristin Davis) untimely death leads to her recruitment as a Christmas angel. Her first task is to help a struggling singer (Eric McCormack) use his music to heal old wounds.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250629120000 +0000" stop="20250629140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">One Christmas Eve</title>
    <desc>A series of mishaps disturbs the plans of a recently divorced mom (Anne Heche) for her two kids on their first Christmas without dad.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250629140000 +0000" stop="20250629160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Checkin' It Twice</title>
    <desc>Sparks fly between a hockey player and a real estate agent after he moves into a cottage in her family's backyard.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250629160000 +0000" stop="20250629180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Holiday Touchdown: A Chiefs Love Story</title>
    <desc>Chiefs superfan Alana tries to win the Fan of the Year Award as a Christmas gift for her family, falling in love with someone in the Chiefs front office along the way.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250629180000 +0000" stop="20250629200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Three Wise Men and a Baby</title>
    <desc>Three brothers get the surprise of their lives when they are forced to work together and care for a baby over the holidays.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250629200000 +0000" stop="20250629220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Haul Out the Holly</title>
    <desc>Emily comes home to visit her parents, only to discover they're leaving for a trip of their own. While staying at their house for the holidays, Emily meets members of the community who want her to join in the neighborhood's Christmas festivities.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250629220000 +0000" stop="20250630000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Machu Picchu Proposal</title>
    <desc>Katie helps plan her brother's proposal atop Machu Picchu. When the proposal is ruined by spontaneous Chef Carlos, Katie enlists Carlos to help her find the most romantic spot in all of Peru. Stars Rhiannon Fish and Alec Santos.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-29</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630000000 +0000" stop="20250630020000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Christmas Getaway</title>
    <desc>After a surprising breakup with her boyfriend, a travel writer decides to go on the picturesque Christmas vacation planned for the two of them, alone.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630020000 +0000" stop="20250630040000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Christmas Detour</title>
    <desc>Two travelers become linked when a snowstorm grounds their flight in Buffalo. Paige desperately needs to find a way to New York City to meet her fiance's parents, and it's up to Dylan, a fellow passenger and a guy she can't stand, to get her there.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630040000 +0000" stop="20250630060000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Cozy Christmas Inn</title>
    <desc>A real estate executive travels to Alaska during the holidays to acquire a bed-and-breakfast, only to discover it's owned by her ex. She's soon falling in love with the town and quite possibly him all over again.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630060000 +0000" stop="20250630063000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche decides to sell her house, and the roommates prepare to go their separate ways.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630063000 +0000" stop="20250630070000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche decides to sell her house, and the roommates prepare to go their separate ways.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630070000 +0000" stop="20250630073000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Dorothy consults medical experts about her chronic fatigue, which raises concern in Rose and Sophia.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630073000 +0000" stop="20250630080000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Harry Weston recommends a specialist who diagnoses Dorothy's illness.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630080000 +0000" stop="20250630083000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Blanche's unmarried daughter announces her desire to have a baby.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630083000 +0000" stop="20250630090000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">The Golden Girls</title>
    <desc>Rose has to go and get a job when she loses her late husband's pension, where she is confronted for the first time by ageism.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630090000 +0000" stop="20250630093000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Frasier</title>
    <desc>Realizing that he has no friends other than his brother, Frasier makes an on-air appeal for a new pal.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630093000 +0000" stop="20250630100000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Frasier</title>
    <desc>Daphne decides to move into a place of her own after Frasier forbids her boyfriend's overnight visits.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630100000 +0000" stop="20250630103000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>The football players think they're doomed when Cheyenne serves the wrong kind of potato salad at the traditional pregame dinner.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630103000 +0000" stop="20250630110000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Reba's ex-husband becomes jealous when she calls a plumber to fix a faucet; Cheyenne "moons" Van's teammates.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630110000 +0000" stop="20250630113000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>Kyra does not want to spend time with her father since it includes Barbra Jean; Cheyenne and Van plan to move out.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630113000 +0000" stop="20250630120000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Reba</title>
    <desc>When Van fails a history test due to the pressure of being a star football player, Reba steps in to tutor him.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630120000 +0000" stop="20250630140000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Heidelberg Holiday</title>
    <desc>Heidi Heidelberg receives a dream opportunity to sell her beautiful, handmade glass ornaments at the prestigious Heidelberg Christmas Market in Germany. While there, she meets Lukas, a local artisan who helps her reconnect with her lost heritage.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630140000 +0000" stop="20250630160000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Gingerbread Miracle</title>
    <desc>A man and an old high school friend try to sell his uncle's business -- a Mexican bakery that's famous for magical gingerbread cookies that grant wishes.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630160000 +0000" stop="20250630180000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A Biltmore Christmas</title>
    <desc>A magical hourglass sends modern-day screenwriter Lucy Hardgrove to the set of the 1947 holiday movie classic "His Merry Wife!" However, before she can return to the present, Lucy must make things right or threaten to alter the future forever.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630180000 +0000" stop="20250630200000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sense, Sensibility &amp; Snowmen</title>
    <desc>Christmas party planners Ella and her sister Marianne clash with client Edward, a not-so-jolly toy company CEO.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630200000 +0000" stop="20250630220000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">A '90s Christmas</title>
    <desc>A workaholic lawyer destined to spend Christmas alone is transported back to 1999 after an unexpected run in with a particularly wise ride-share driver.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250630220000 +0000" stop="20250701000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Sugarplummed</title>
    <desc>When Emily wishes for a perfect Christmas like the ones found in the popular Sugarplum movies, she's shocked when Sugarplum herself appears to help her fulfill it.</desc>
    <date>2025-06-30</date>
  </programme>
  <programme channel="403490" start="20250701000000 +0000" stop="20250702000000 +0000">
    <title lang="zh">Coyote Creek Christmas</title>
    <desc>An event planner discovers Christmas magic with a charming father-son duo while throwing a themed Christmas party at her family's inn.</desc>
    <date>2025-07-01</date>
  </programme>
</tv>
